<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cockatrice_carddatabase version="3">
<sets>
<set>
<name>JVC</name>
<longname>Jazzy Vintage Cube</longname>
<settype></settype>
</set>
</sets>
<cards>

<card>
 <name>The Wellspring of Destiny</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add C.
T: Add G or W for each creature you own on an Adventure.
GW, T: Search your library for a creature card with an Adventure, reveal it, put it into your hand, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Swamp Lurker</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G // G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Plant  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
--- 
Take the initiative.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Palantir of Qotrixi</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Palantir of Qotrixi enters, scry 2.
Sacrifice Palantir of Qotrixi: Add two mana in any combination of colors.
Dredge 2 (If you would draw a card, you mill two cards instead. If you do, return this card from your graveyard to your hand. Otherwise, draw a card.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Steamroll the Session</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>WG</color>
 <manacost>XGW</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Convoke (Your creatures can help cast this spell. Each creature you tap while casting this spell pays for 1 or one mana of that creature’s color.)
Improvise (Your artifacts can help cast this spell. Each artifact you tap after you’re done activating mana abilities pays for 1.)
Take the initiative X times.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Seti, Rebel Leader</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>M</color>
 <manacost>2W // GU</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Soldier  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever a historic permanent you control enters, create X 1/1 white Human Warrior creature tokens, where X is that permanent’s mana value. Do this at most once each turn.
--- 
Choose a permanent type. Until end of turn, whenever a permanent you control of the chosen type enters, you may draw a card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Aeomar, Spiritfarer</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>2G // 2G</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Elk Spirit  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Ward 3
You may cast Adventure spells from your graveyard.
--- 
Draw a card for each creature you control and each card you own on an Adventure.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Sage of Vainamoinen</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G // 1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Snow Creature - Human Wizard  // Sorcery - Adventure </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever a creature you control attacks, venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
--- 
Search your library for a creature card, reveal it, put it into your hand, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ruthless Kingmaker</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Advisor </type>
 <pt>4/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Ruthless Kingmaker enters, you get a monarchy counter.
At the beginning of each player’s upkeep, if one of that player’s opponents has the most monarchy counters, each creature that player controls connives.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vammatar</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>BBB</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Nightmare </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>You get a poison counter: Choose one — 
• Target creature gets +1/+0 and gains first strike and toxic 1 until end of turn. (Players dealt combat damage by that creature this turn get a poison counter.)
• Target creature gets -0/-1 until end of turn.
• Target player draws a card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Morrigan</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1RR</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Summon Harpy Legend</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
Whenever you discard a land card, add two mana of any color.
Whenever you discard a creature card, create a 2/2 red Harpy creature token with flying.
Whenever you discard a noncreature, nonland card, exile the top two cards of your library. Until end of your next turn, you may play cards exiled this way.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Beckoned to Assimilate</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Create a token that’s a copy of target creature card in your graveyard. It gains haste. Sacrifice it at the beginning of the next end step.
Flashback—1R, Discard three cards (You may cast this card from your graveyard for its flashback cost. Then exile it.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Zheng Yi Sao, Red Fleet Queen</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>2B</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Ninja Pirate </type>
 <pt>3/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Ninjutsu B
When Zheng Yi Sao, Red Fleet Queen deals combat damage to a player, search that player’s library for a card and exile it face down. Then that player shuffles. For the rest of the game, you may look at and play the exiled card for as long as it remains exiled, and you may spend mana as though it were mana of any type to cast that spell.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Morgaine, the Curseweaver</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>UB</color>
 <manacost>UB</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Elf Warlock </type>
 <pt>1/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Deathtouch
UB: The next instant or sorcery spell you cast this turn gains cipher. (You may exile that spell card encoded on a creature you control as it resolves. Whenever that creature deals combat damage to a player, its controller may cast a copy of the encoded card without paying its mana cost.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>It's Time to DDDD-Duel</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>UR</color>
 <manacost>UR</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>The next spell you cast this turn gains storm. (When you cast that spell, copy it for each spell cast before it this turn. You may choose new targets for the copies. Copies of permanent spells become tokens.)
Flashback 1UR (You may cast this card from your graveyard for its flashback cost. Then exile it.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Spoils of Conquest</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>WR</color>
 <manacost>1RW</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Create a Treasure token. (It’s an artifact with “T, Sacrifice this artifact: Add one mana of any color.”)
Gravestorm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each permanent put into a graveyard this turn.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>A Single Wish Will Be Granted</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill A Single Wish Will Be Granted as an instant if you’ve played a land and cast at least one artifact, creature, enchantment, instant, and sorcery spell this turn. When you do, choose a Magic the Gathering card, conjure a copy of it, then cast the copy without paying its mana cost.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Sleepless Oracle</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Wizard </type>
 <pt>0/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When you cast Sleepless Oracle, exile the bottom card of your library.
T: Scry X, where X is the number of cards you own in exile. 
Escape—Exile two other cards from your graveyard.  (You may cast this card from your graveyard for its escape cost.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Dragon God's Revenge</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>At the beginning of your upkeep, fulfill The Dragon God’s Revenge if there are a total of ten or more creatures and/or planeswalkers on the battlefield. When you do, destroy all creatures and planeswalkers, then each opponent loses 5 life and you gain 5 life.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Carissa Brierborn</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Satyr Druid </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Carissa Brierborn enters, take the initiative.
T: Create X 1/1 green Plant Spirit creature tokens with haste, where X is the number of rooms you’ve entered this turn.
Whenever you complete a dungeon, you may pay U/B. If you do, each creature you control connives.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Thallid Nursery</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>At the beginning of your upkeep, you may mill two cards.
Discard a card: Return up to one target land card from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Terraform Engine</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>RG</color>
 <manacost>RG</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>1: Shuffle up to one target land card from your graveyard into your library.
2, Sacrifice a land: Search your library for a land card, put that card onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Dousing Grove</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>When The Dousing Grove enters, choose one — 
• Counter target spell.
• Target permanent you control gains hexproof until end of turn.
T: Add G or U.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Guardfish Island</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Island </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>When Guardfish Island enters, draw a card.
(T: Add U.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mining Installation</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>If you control no lands, sacrifice Mining Installation.
Sacrifice a land: Creature a Treasure token. (It’s an artifact with “T, Sacrifice this artifact: Add one mana of any color.”)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Cascading Creation</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>At the beginning of your upkeep, reveal the top card of your library. If it’s a land card, put it onto the battlefield and repeat this process.
G, Sacrifice Cascading Creation: Until end of turn, spells you cast have cascade. Activate only if you’ve fulfilled a prophecy.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Belugma, Queen of the Marsh</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature Land - Island Swamp Turtle </type>
 <pt>0/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>(T: Add U or B.)
Islandwalk, swampwalk. (This creature can’t be blocked as long as defending player controls an Island or a Swamp.
1UB: Monstrosity 4  (If this creature isn’t monstrous, put four +1/+1 counters on it and it becomes monstrous.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Damaged Stargate</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add C.
T, Return a nonland permanent you control to its owner’s hand: You may put a land card from your hand onto the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Seraph of Mercy</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>3W</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Angel </type>
 <pt>2/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
Flying
When Seraph of Mercy enters the battlefield, return to the battlefield all non-Angel permanent cards in your graveyard that were put there from the battlefield this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Terrestrial Damacy</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>RG</color>
 <manacost>RG</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Elemental </type>
 <pt>5/5</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Trample, haste
When Terrestrial Damacy enters, sacrifice all lands you control.
When Terrestrial Damacy leaves the battlefield, return all land cards from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Time Tomb</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>When The Time Tomb enters, search your library for a card, put that card into your graveyard, then shuffle.
T: Add B.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vyre, Prince of Pain</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Devil </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Discard a card: Create a 1/1 red Devil creature token with “When this creature dies, it deals 1 damage to any target.”
Hellbent — As long as you have no cards in hand, creatures you control have menace and haste.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Hell of a Time</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Debauchery — At the beginning of each end step, create a 1/1 red Devil creature token for each card you’ve discarded this turn. They have “When this creature dies, it deals 1 damage to any target.”</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Arphoros, the Fallen One</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>4RR</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Enchantment Creature - God </type>
 <pt>6/6</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>As long as the number of creature cards in your graveyard is less than six, Arphoros, the Fallen One isn’t a creature.
When Arphoros, the Fallen One enters or attacks, it deals 6 damage divided as you choose among any number of targets.
Escape—RR, Exile six cards from your graveyard.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Lunatic Visitation</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Lunatic Visitation deals 4 damage to target creature or planeswalker. Its controller enters a nightmare. (The nightmare ends when that player enters a dream or another nightmare.)
Madness R (If you discard this card, discard it into exile. When you do, cast it for its madness cost or put it into your graveyard.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Fissure the Blood Glacier</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Snow Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Add RRG.
Fertilize (When this card is put into your graveyard from your hand or library, you may return up to one target land card from your graveyard to the battlefield.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Flight of the Dusk Hallows</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>4RR</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Flight of the Dusk Hallows deals 1 damage to any target.
Exile the top card of your library. You may play that card this turn. 
Add one mana of any color.
Gravestorm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each permanent put into a graveyard this turn. You may choose new targets for the copies.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Explode the Singularity</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>2R</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Return target instant or sorcery card from your graveyard to your hand.
Storm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each spell cast before it this turn. You may choose new targets for the copies.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Santeria</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>XBB</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Macabre (This spell costs 1 less to cast for each permanent put into a graveyard from the battlefield this turn.)
Each player discards X cards, draws X cards, then each player creates X Blood tokens. (They’re artifacts with “1, T, Discard a card, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a card.”)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Quid Pro Quo</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Destroy target nonland permanent. Its controller draws cards equal to its mana value.
2W, Exile Quid Pro Quo from your graveyard: You get a monarchy counter.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Phyrexian Parasite</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>2B</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Phyrexian Horror </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Phyrexian Parasite enters, create three black 1/1 Phyrexian Thrall artifact creature tokens.
Sacrifice an artifact or creature: Target opponent loses 1 life and you gain 1 life.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Gloomwing Pilgrim</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Warlock </type>
 <pt>3/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Gloomwing Pilgrim enters, surveil 3.
Whenever a permanent an opponent controls is put into a graveyard from the battlefield, you may pay 1 life. If you do, return target instant or sorcery card from your graveyard to your hand.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Black Sacrement</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Add one mana of any color.
Gravestorm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each permanent put into a graveyard this turn. You may choose new targets for the copies.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Morning Witch Hunt</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>W</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Investigate (Create a colorless Clue artifact token with “2, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a card.”)
Gravestorm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each permanent put into a graveyard this turn.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Crypt Crack Key</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>3</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Plunder target opponent for 1. (Look at the top card of target opponent’s library. You may exile it face down. If you do, you may play that card using mana of any color for as long as it remains exiled.)
Sacrifice an artifact: Create a 1/1 black Bat creature token with flying.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Holder of the Scales</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Angel </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
At the beginning of your upkeep, each player may put a historic permanent card from their hand or graveyard onto the battlefield. (Artifacts, legendaries, and Sagas are historic.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Current Conduit</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>W</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Human Artificer </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever an ability of another permanent you control triggers, put a +1/+1 counter on Current Conduit.
Remove three +1/+1 counters from Current Conduit: Copy target activated or triggered ability you control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Urza's Sushi Bar</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Land - Urza’s Mountain Plains </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>(T: Add R or W.)
T, Sacrifice an artifact: Create a Food token. (It’s an artifact with “2, T, Sacrifice this artifact: You gain 3 life.”)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Threaded Angel</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Construct Horror </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Threaded Angel enters the battlefield, put a doom counter on target creature.
When Threaded Angel dies, destroy target creature with a doom counter on it.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Black Market Fence</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Rogue </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Haste
T: Target opponent gains control of another target permanent you control. Create X Treasure tokens, where X is the mana value of that permanent. (They’re artifacts with “T, Sacrifice this artifact: Add one mana of any color.”)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Witch King Karanak</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Nightmare Spirit </type>
 <pt>1/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Other creatures you control have haunt. (When that creature dies, exile it haunting target creature.)
Whenever a haunted creature an opponent controls dies, return all creature cards haunting that creature to the battlefield under your control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Spark Excavator</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Construct </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice Spark Excavator: It deals 1 damage to any target.
1: Turbocharge. (Each other artifact you control has all activated and triggered abilities of this artifact until end of turn. Sacrifice this artifact at the beginning of the next end step.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Jace's Simulacrum</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>4</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Construct </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever another artifact you control enters, you may draw a card.
T: Turbocharge target artifact you control. (Each other artifact you control has all activated and triggered abilities of that artifact until end of turn. Sacrifice that artifact at the beginning of the next end step.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Feral Fae</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Faerie Rogue </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
When Feral Fae enters, choose one —
• Copy target instant or sorcery spell. You may choose new targets for the copy.
• Change the target of target spell or ability with a single target.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Hadestown</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add R.
T, Discard a card: Add RR.
Hellbent Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, if you have no cards in hand, Hadestown deals 2 damage to any target.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Silrien, Lady of Gifts</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Elf Artificer </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Silrien, Lady of Gifts enters, create a Treasure token for each legendary permanent you control.
Whenever you sacrifice a token, you may scry 1.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Living Tribunal</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Avatar </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>T: Venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
Whenever you cast an Adventure spell or venture into the dungeon, add one mana of any color. You don’t lose this mana as steps and phases end.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mystic Convocation</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>R: Put an artifact or creature card from your hand onto the battlefield. Sacrifice it at the beginning of the next phase.
GW: The next time a permanent you control would be sacrificed this turn, instead you may return it to its owner’s hand. </text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ring of the Mad Mage</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>8</manacost>
 <cmc>8</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Ring of the Mad Mage costs 8 less to cast if you’ve completed The Dungeon of the Mad Mage.
T: Choose three Magic: The Gathering cards at random, then create a copy of each of those cards. You may cast the copies without paying their mana costs.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Tides of Fate</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>2U</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, you may put a permanent card from your hand onto the battlefield.
At the beginning of the end step, sacrifice Tides of Fate.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Nexus Arcanus</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>2UU</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>At the beginning of your precombat main phase, scry 1.
Divination — Whenever you look at cards from the top of a library, choose one — 
• Add that much mana in any combination of colors.
• Draw that many cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ocean of Dreams</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1UU</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Ocean of Dreams enters, scry 3. (To scry 3, look at the top three cards of your library, then put any number of them on the bottom of your library and the rest on top in any order.)
Whenever you tap a land, add G, U, or R.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Replicant Assembly</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>3</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Create a 1/1 colorless Construct artifact creature token.
3: Turbocharge. (Each other artifact you control has all activated and triggered abilities of this artifact until end of turn. Sacrifice this artifact at the beginning of the next end step.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Chrome Cathedral</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>Chrome Cathedral enters tapped and doesn’t untap during your untap step.
Whenever an artifact you control enters, you may untap Chrome Cathedral.
T: Add C.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Reverse Entropy Pyramid</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>4</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Create a token that’s a copy of target artifact card in your graveyard.
4: Turbocharge. (Each other artifact you control has all activated and triggered abilities of this artifact until end of turn. Sacrifice this artifact at the beginning of the next end step.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mox Bismuth</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>0</manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add one mana of any color and put an awakening counter on Mox Bismuth. 
Whenever you tap Mox Bismuth for mana, if there are four or more awakening counters on it, target opponent creates a token that’s a copy of It That Betrays. (It’s an 11/11 colorless Eldrazi creature with “Annihilator 2”, and “Whenever an opponent sacrifices a permanent, put that card onto the battlefield under your control.”)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Predator City</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>Ascend (If you control ten or more permanents, you get the city’s blessing for the rest of the game.)
T: Add C.
Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, if you have the city’s blessing, you may pay 2. If you do, destroy target land.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Accursed Dramargu</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1BB</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Nightmare </type>
 <pt>6/5</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying, trample
Ward—Pay 4 life. (Whenever this creature becomes the target of a spell or ability an opponent controls, counter it unless that player pays 4 life.)
Whenever an opponent casts or copies a spell, that player draws two cards and loses 2 life.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Old Henry</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Pirate </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Skulk (This creature can’t be blocked by creatures with greater power.)
At the beginning of each end step, plunder target opponent for X, where X is the number of crimes you’ve committed against that player this turn. (Look at the top X cards of that player’s library. You may exile them face down. If you do, you may play those cards using mana of any color for as long as they remain exiled.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Draconic Avarice</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Target player reveals their hand. You choose a noncreature, nonland card from it. That player discards that card. Create a Treasure token.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Seductive Bargain</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Search your library for a card, put that card into your hand, then shuffle.
Target opponent draws two cards and creates two Treasure tokens.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Embrace the Nightmare</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>4BB</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Delve (Each card you exile from your graveyard while casting this spell pays for 1.)
Exchange the contents of your hand and your graveyard.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Scroll of Unending Bureaucracy</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>3</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Scroll of Unending Bureaucracy costs 3 less to cast if you control an Advisor.
Whenever a player casts a spell, that player puts the cards in their hand on the bottom of their library in a random order, then draws that many cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Curse of the Sovereign</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>WB</color>
 <manacost>WB</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Curse of the Sovereign enters the battlefield, you get a monarchy counter.
You are your own opponent.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Discovery of Lost Antiquity</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill The Discovery of Lost Antiquity at the beginning of your upkeep if you control three creatures that share a color each with power two or less. When you do, search your library for a historic permanent card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Triumph of the Elder Dragon</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill Triumph of the Elder Dragon as a sorcery as long as you there are five or more different colors among permanents you control. When you do, search your library and/or graveyard for a white card, a blue card, a black card, a red card, and a green card. Reveal those cards, put them into your hand, then shuffle. Add WUBRG.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Thion Qisalor, Realm of Stars</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add U or R.
T: Create a 1/1 blue and red Faerie creature token with flying. Activate this ability only during an opponent’s turn and only if you control a spell.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Alter Fate</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>UU</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Choose one —
• Counter target spell.
• Change the target of target spell with a single target.
• Counter the fulfillment of a prophecy.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Rajesh, Imperial Power Broker</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Cat Artificer </type>
 <pt>1/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Rajesh, Imperial Power Broker enters the battlefield, you get a monarchy counter.
T: Give target opponent one of your monarchy counters.
Whenever an opponent gains a monarchy counter, create three Treasure tokens.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Merciless Chamberlain</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Advisor </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Merciless Chamberlain enters, you get a monarchy counter.
Sacrifice a creature: Monstrosity 4. (If this creature isn’t monstrous, put four +1/+1 counters on it and it becomes monstrous.)
Whenever Merciless Chamberlain becomes monstrous, give target opponent one of your monarchy counters.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Wheel of Time</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>BR</color>
 <manacost>1BR</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Enchantment - Saga </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Neverending story (As this enters and after your draw step, add a lore counter. Remove all lore counters after III.)
I — Each player discards their hand.
II — Each player draws seven cards.
III — Each player loses 1 life for each card in their hand.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vamgrund, the Dreadflame</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WBR</color>
 <manacost>RWB</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Orc Warlock </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>T: The next spell you cast this turn gains gravestorm. (When you cast that spell, copy it for each permanent put into a graveyard this turn. Copies of permanent spells become tokens.)
Unearth RWB (RWB: Return this card from your graveyard to the battlefield. It gains haste. Exile it at the beginning of the end step or if it would leave the battlefield. Unearth only as a sorcery.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Wolgan, the Further</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G // G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Barbarian  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>2/3</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever you expand the frontier, you may mill two cards, then return up to one card from your graveyard to your hand.
--- 
You may sacrifice a land. If you do, search your library for a land card, put that card onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Temur Spirit Conduit</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Shaman </type>
 <pt>1/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>T: Venture into the dungeon, then scry X, where X is the number of rooms you’ve entered in the current dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Inspiring Gleeman</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Halfling Bard </type>
 <pt>0/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Tap an untapped creature you control: Venture into the dungeon (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Reckless Dungeoneers</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Cleric Rogue Warrior Wizard </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever you venture into the dungeon, put a +1/+1 counter on Reckless Dungeoneers.
Cumulative upkeep—Venture into the dungeon. (At the beginning of your upkeep, put an age counter on this creature, then sacrifice it unless you pay its upkeep cost for each age counter on it.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Unsheathe the Cursed Cutlass</name>
 <set rarity="common">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Kindred Instant - Pirate </type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Destroy target non-Pirate creature.
Prowl 0 (You may cast this for its prowl cost if you dealt combat damage to a player this turn with a Pirate.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Whims of the Tyrant</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Target player reveals their hand. You choose a nonland card from it. That player discards that card. You lose 2 life. If you’re part of the hive, you may choose up to two nonland cards instead. (You’re part of the hive when your library has at most half as many cards as it did at the start of the game.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Secret Lagoon</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Island Swamp </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>You may have Secret Lagoon enter tapped. When you do, plunder target opponent for 1. (Look at the top card of target opponent’s library. You may exile it face down. If you do, you may play that card using mana of any color for as long as it remains exiled.)
(T: Add U or B.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Guiding Tree</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Mountain Forest </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>You may have Guiding Tree enter tapped. When you do, target creature you control explores. (Reveal the top card of your library. Put that card into your hand if it’s a land. Otherwise, put a +1/+1 counter on that creature, then put the card back or put it into your graveyard.)
(T: Add R or G.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Nythrodain, the Library City</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add W.
T: Add W for each historic permanent you control. (Artifacts, legendaries, and Sagas are historic.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ominous Gate</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Swamp Mountain </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>You may have Ominous Gate enter tapped. When you do, discard a card, then draw a card.
(T: Add B or R.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Nexus of Lies</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Plains Swamp </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>You may have Nexus of Lies enter tapped. When you do, target opponent sacrifices a permanent and draws two cards.
(T: Add W or B.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Humble Beginning</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Forest Plains </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>You may have Humble Beginning enter tapped. When you do, venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
(T: Add G or W.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Noxious Dwelling</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Swamp Forest </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>You may have Noxious Dwelling enter tapped. When you do, mill five cards.
(T: Add B or G.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Striding Stones</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Mountain Planes </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>You may have Striding Stones enter tapped. When you do, investigate. (Create a colorless Clue artifact token with “2, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a card.”)
(T: Add R or W.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Golden Planetarium</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Plains Island </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>You may have Golden Planetarium enter tapped. When you do, create a 1/1 colorless Thopter artifact creature token with flying.
(T: Add W or U.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Soulfire Monastery</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Island Mountain </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>You may have Soulfire Monastery enter tapped. When you do, put up to one target instant or sorcery card from your graveyard on top of your library.
(T: Add U or R.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Torhild, the Glorious</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>W</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Warrior </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Torhild, the Glorious enters, take the initiative.
Whenever you complete a dungeon, put a level counter on Torhild.. [1/1]
[level 1] Whenever Torhild attacks, create a 4/4 white Angel creature token with flying and vigilance that’s tapped and attacking. [2/2]
[level 2+] Whenever a creature you control attacks, create a 4/4 white Angel creature token with flying and vigilance that’s tapped and attacking. [3/3]
LEVEL 1
2/2

LEVEL 2+
3/3
</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Pirate Class</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>UB</color>
 <manacost>UB</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment - Class </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>(Gain the next level as a sorcery to add its ability.)
Whenever a creature you control deals combat damage to a player, plunder that player for 1. (Look at the top card of that player’s library. You may exile it face down. If you do, you may play that card using mana of any color for as long as it remains exiled.)
UB: Level 2
Whenever you plunder, create a Treasure token.
UB: Level 3
At the beginning of your upkeep, draw a card for each permanent you control but do not own.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Bottle O'Rum</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Kindred Artifact - Pirate Equipment </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Equipped creature has haste and is a Pirate in addition to its other types.
You may exert equipped creature as it attacks. When you do, plunder target opponent for 3. (Look at the top three cards of target opponent’s library. You may exile them face down. If you do, you may play those cards using mana of any color for as long as they remain exiled.)
Equip 0</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Neon Freebooter</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Ninja Pirate </type>
 <pt>1/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Neon Freebooter enters, plunder target opponent for 2. (Look at the top two cards of target opponent’s library. You may exile them face down. If you do, you may play those cards using mana of any color for as long as they remain exiled.)
Whenever you play a card you do not own, the owner of that card reveals their hand and you may choose a nonland card from it. That player discards that card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Bloodmoon Shinobi</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1BB</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Vampire Ninja Pirate </type>
 <pt>3/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Ninjutsu B (B, Return an unblocked attacker you control to hand: Put this card onto the battlefield from your hand tapped and attacking.)
When Bloodmoon Shinobi deals combat damage to a player, search your library for a card, then shuffle and put that card on top. You lose 2 life. </text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Collapse of the Kingdom</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill Collapse of the Kingdom as a sorcery if a player has three or more monarchy counters. When you do, you get an emblem with, “Creatures you control get +1/+1 and have lifelink and menace.”</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Expand the Hoard</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Choose one — 
• Search your library for an artifact card, put that card into your graveyard, then shuffle your library.
• Create three Treasure tokens.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Gurren Lagann</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WR</color>
 <manacost>RW</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact - Vehicle </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Vigilance, haste
Gurren Lagann has all activated abilities and triggered abilities of all other artifacts you control.
When Gurren Lagann attacks, untap all artifacts you control.
Crew 2</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Real First Mate</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Bird Pirate </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
When The Real First Mate enters or leaves the battlefield, plunder target opponent for 1. (Look at the top card of target opponent’s library. You may exile it face down. If you do, you may play that card using mana of any color for as long as it remains exiled.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Doom of Moria</name>
 <set rarity="rare" splitterPath="/The Doom of Moria.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <related attach="attach">Durin's Bane</related>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment - Saga </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>
---
(Back): Durin's Bane</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Durin's Bane</name>
 <set rarity="rare" splitterPath="/Durin's Bane.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color>BR</color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Demon </type>
 <pt>5/5</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Trample, reach
When Durin’s Bane enters, destroy all Dwarves.
When Durin’s Bane dies, destroy target Wizard.
---
(Front): The Doom of Moria</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ambitious Reconstructor</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Drawf Artificer </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>1R, T: Create a token that’s a copy of target artifact card in your graveyard. If it’s a creature, it gains haste. Sacrifice it at the beginning of the next end step.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Stylish Strike</name>
 <set rarity="common">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Target creature gets -2/-2 until end of turn.
Skirmish — If an opponent controls a spell, that creature gets -4/-4 until end of turn instead. Create two  Treasure tokens.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Hornswoggle</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Return target nonland permanent to its owner’s hand.
Skirmish — If an opponent controls a spell, surveil 4. (Look at the top four cards of your library, then put any number of them into your graveyard and the rest on top of your library in any order.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Jin-Gitaxias' Manipulation</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>H/UH/U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Counter any number of spells target player controls. That player gets a poison counter.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Ninth Gate</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T, Pay 2 life: Add CC.
Whenever you pay any amount of life, you may mill that many cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Desperate Contract</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Target player draws two cards and loses 2 life.
Fateful hour — If you have 5 or less life, you may flip a coin. If you win the flip, take an extra turn after this one. If you lose the flip, sacrifice all permanents you control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Jargrumir Chainbuckle</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Dwarf Artificer </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever Jargrumir Chainbuckle enters, take the initiative.
W, T, Sacrifice any number of artifacts: Search your library for an artifact card with mana value less than or equal to the combined mana value of the sacrificed artifacts, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Urza's Gourmet</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Urza’s Construct </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever Urza’s Gourmet or another nontoken permanent enters under your control, create a Food token.
If you would gain life, instead put that many +1/+1 counters on target artifact creature you control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ghirapur Renagade</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>2R</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Artificer </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Haste
T: Turbocharge target artifact you control. (Each other artifact you control has all activated and triggered abilities of that artifact until end of turn. Sacrifice it at the beginning of the next end step.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Jin Huo, the Swift Sunrise</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Bird Monk </type>
 <pt>1/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying, prowess
Soulfire (Whenever this creature deals combat damage, choose an instant or sorcery card in your graveyard with mana value less than or equal to the amount of damage dealt. You may cast it this turn. If that spell would be put into your graveyard, exile it instead.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Face Scraper</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Phyrexian Horror </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Haste
Face Scraper can’t block.
Phylactery (When this creature enters the battlefield, put a phylactery counter on up to one target artifact you control. You may cast this card from your graveyard by sacrificing an artifact with a phylactery counter on it in addition to paying its other costs.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Attachment</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Incarnation </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Haunt (When this creature dies, exile it haunting target creature.)
Whenever the creature Attachment haunts dies, that creature’s controller discards their hand, then draws seven cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Glass Emanation</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>0</manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Glass Emanation enters, draw a card. 
T, Sacrifice Glass Emanation: Add one mana of any color.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Enki, the Regaler</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>3G // XGG</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Avatar  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>You may cast copies of Adventure spells from among the Adventures of creatures you control.
--- 
Discover X (Exile cards from the top of your library until you exile a nonland card with mana value X or less. Cast it without paying its mana cost or put it into your hand. Put the rest on the bottom in a random order.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Jotun Dreadlord</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G // 1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Giant Warrior  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>2/3</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>When Jotun Dreadlord enters the battlefield, you may destroy up to one target artifact or enchantment.
--- 
Destroy target artifact or enchantment.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Forerunner of the Machine</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WR</color>
 <manacost>2RW</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Phyrexian Horror </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever you expand the frontier, reveal cards from the top of your library until you reveal an artifact card. You may put that card onto the battlefield, and the rest on the bottom of your library in a random order. When you do, Forerunner of the Machine deals damage equal to that artifact’s mana value to target creature and that much damage to you. (You expand the frontier when a land you control enters that does not share a name with another land you control.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Pyramid Curator</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Sphinx Artificer Wizard </type>
 <pt>1/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever you cast a historic spell, scry 1. (Artifacts, legendaries, and Sagas are historic.)
Divination — Whenever you look at cards from the top of a library, create that many Treasure tokens. (They’re artifacts with “T, Sacrifice this artifact: Add one mana of any color.”)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Bhaskara, the Hierophant</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Elephant Wizard </type>
 <pt>1/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Bhaskara, the Hierophant enters the battlefield, create a Blood, Clue, Food, or Treasure token.
Whenever you sacrifice an artifact, you may draw a card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ravnican Renaissance</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>UUU</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Convoke (Your creatures can help cast this spell. Each creature you tap while casting this spell pays for 1 or one mana of that creature’s color.)
Until end of turn, whenever you draw a card, add one mana of any color.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Faerie Parry</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Cleave 1U (You may cast this spell for its cleave cost. If you do, remove the words in square brackets.)
Counter target [noncreature] spell [unless its controller pays 3].</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Cracked Mirror Cultist</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Snow Artifact Creature - Warlock </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Lands and artifacts you control are snow in addition to their other types.
Sacrifice a snow permanent: If you’ve fulfilled a prophecy, add two mana in any combination of colors. Otherwise, add one mana of any color.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Swiftbeacon Priestess</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>W</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Elf Cleric </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
When Swiftbeacon Priestess enters, venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
Whenever you venture into the dungeon, you may return another target permanent you control to its owner’s hand.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Allomatic Battlemage</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Construct Warrior </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever you venture into the dungeon, put a +1/+1 counter on Allomatic Battlemage. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
Sacrifice an artifact: Venture into the dungeon.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Young Phelddagrif</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Phelddagrif </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying, trample
When Young Phelddagrif enters, venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
Whenever you complete a dungeon, you gain X life and draw X cards, where X is the number of dungeons you’ve completed.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Nightbreeze Avenger</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Faerie Rogue </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
Flying
When Nightbreeze Avenger enters the battlefield, gain control of target activated or triggered ability. You may choose new targets for it.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Essence Ice</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>0</manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Snow Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Essence Ice is put into a graveyard from anywhere, you gain 1 life, add one mana of any color, and draw a card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Underworld Fleshhook</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Skeleton Demon </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice Underworld Fleshhook: Underworld Fleshhook deals 2 damage to any target.
Whenever you sacrifice a Blood artifact, you may pay 1 life. If you do, return Underworld Fleshhook from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mausoleum Fiend</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>WB</color>
 <manacost>WB</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Nightmare </type>
 <pt>3/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever an opponent draws a card, venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
Whenever you complete a dungeon, target opponent loses 1 life for each card in their hand and you gain life equal to the life lost this way.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Nyx Starfall</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>0</manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Enchantment Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T, Sacrifice Nyx Starfall: Choose a color. Add an amount of mana of that color equal to your devotion to that color. (Each that in the mana costs of permanents you control counts toward your devotion to that.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Dead Men Tell No Tales</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>2B</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Plunder target opponent for 1. (Look at the top card of target opponent’s library. You may exile it face down. If you do, you may play that card using mana of any color for as long as it remains exiled.)
Gravestorm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each permanent put into a graveyard this turn. You may choose new targets for the copies.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Spirit of Discovery</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WG</color>
 <manacost>4GW</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment Creature - Dragon Spirit </type>
 <pt>4/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
Whenever another nontoken creature you control enters, you may discover N, where N is that creature’s toughness minus 1.
Legacy 1GW (1GW, Exile this card from your graveyard: Create a token that’s a copy of it, except it’s not a creature. Activate only as a sorcery.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Deconstruction Drone</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Eldrazi </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Devoid (This card has no color.)
1: Surveil 1.
2: Venture into the dungeon.
3: Create a 1/1 colorless Eldrazi Scion creature token with “Sacrifice this creature: Add C.”
4: Any number of permanents you control become artifacts in addition to their other types until end of turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Power of Relinquished</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Target creature loses all abilities, becomes an Aura enchantment with “Enchant creature” and “Totem armor.” Attach it to target creature you control. (If enchanted permanent would be destroyed, instead removal all damage from it and destroy the Aura.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Manic Bonfire</name>
 <set rarity="common">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Madness 0 (If you discard this card, discard it into exile. When you do, cast it for its madness cost or put it into your graveyard.)
Manic Bonfire deals 3 damage to any target. If a creature dealt damage this way would die this turn, exile it instead.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Infinite Starfield Guru</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment Creature - Spirit Avatar </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Discard a card: Add one mana of any color.
At the beginning of your upkeep, if you have no cards in hand, exile the top two cards of your library. Until end of turn, you may play those cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Font of the Blood God</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1BB</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Font of the Blood God enters, you get a monarchy counter.
Whenever an opponent casts a spell or draws a card, create a Blood token. (It’s an artifact with “1, T, Discard a card, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a card.”)
Sacrifice an artifact: Add one mana of any color.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Subsume the Host</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Target creature fights itself. When that creature dies this turn, if you’re part of the hive, return it to the battlefield under your control. (You’re part of the hive when your library has at most half as many cards as it did at the start of the game.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Spoocat Bedlam</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>BB</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Create four 0/1 black Cat Spirit creature tokens. They have “Sacrifice this creature: Add one mana of any color.”</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mechanical Inspector</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Detective Construct </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever a player commits a crime, create a Clue token and a tapped Powerstone token. (They are colorless artifact tokens with “2, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a card.” and “T: Add C. This mana can’t be spent to cast a nonartifact spell.” respectively.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Strength of the Party</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>W // W</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever a creature you control enters, venture into the dungeon.
--- 
You can’t lose the game this turn. Until end of turn, damage that would reduce your life total to less than 1 reduces it to 1 instead.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vanguard Captain of Bant</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Aven Warrior </type>
 <pt>2/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
Flying
When Vanguard Captain of Bant enters, untap all nonland permanents you control.
Whenever a creature you control deals combat damage, venture into the dungeon.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Oshaenanore, the Farstone</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add W.
3W, T: Exile target permanent you control, then return it to the battlefield under its owner’s control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Land Ho</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Destroy target nonbasic land.
Plunder that land’s controller for 1. (Look at the top card of that player’s library. You may exile it face down. If you do, you may play that card using mana of any color for as long as it remains exiled.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Night of Horrors</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>BR</color>
 <manacost>3BR</manacost>
 <cmc>5</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Exile a nonland card at random from target player’s graveyard. Until end of turn, you may cast that card from exile without paying its mana cost. Exile Night of Horrors.
Gravestorm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each permanent put into a graveyard this turn. You may choose new targets for the copies.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Acolyte of Yawgmoth</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>2BB</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Phyrexian Knight </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Fear (This creature can’t be blocked except by artifact creatures and/or black creatures.)
Whenever a player draws a card, put a +1/+1 counter on Acolyte of Yawgmoth.
Sacrifice an artifact or creature: Draw a card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Walk the Plank</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Destroy target creature without flying.
Plunder target opponent for X, where X is the number of Islands you control. (Look at the top X cards of target opponent’s library. You may exile them face down. If you do, you may play those cards using mana of any color for as long as they remain exiled.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>White Lotus</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>0</manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When White Lotus enters, add three mana in any combination of colors.
When White Lotus leaves the battlefield, scry 3.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Goblin Aerialist</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Goblin Artificer </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice an artifact: Put a +1/+1 counter on Goblin Aerialist. It gains flying until end of turn.
Whenever Goblin Aerialist deals combat damage to a player, create that many Junk tokens. (They’re artifacts with “T, Sacrifice this artifact: Exile the top card of your library. You may play that card this turn. Activate only as a sorcery.”)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Pyretic Pillage</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>2R</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Destroy target artifact, land, or planeswalker.
Madness—Pay 3 life. (If you discard this card, discard it into exile. When you do, cast it for its madness cost or put it into your graveyard.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Blood Crystal Cavern</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add C.
T, Sacrifice Blood Crystal Cavern: Exile target land. You and that land’s controller each create a Blood token and a Treasure token. </text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Fellbrew Hollow</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add R, W, or B.
Morbid — T: Add RWB. Activate this ability only if a creature died this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Occult Procession</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>XWWW</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Reveal cards from the top of your library until you reveal a nonland permanent card with mana value X or less. If you do, put it into the battlefield, then put another permanent you control on the bottom of its owner’s library.
Gravestorm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each permanent put into a graveyard this turn. You may choose new targets for the copies.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Kindlebone Soulsnatcher</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>4B</manacost>
 <cmc>5</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Scarecrow Warlock </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Macabre (This spell costs 1 less to cast for each permanent put into a graveyard from the battlefield this turn.)
When Kindlebone Soulsnatcher enters, you may cast target instant or sorcery card from your graveyard without paying its mana cost. If you do, exile it as it resolves.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Wind of One Thousand Eyes</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>4W</manacost>
 <cmc>5</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Morbid — Wind of One Thousand Eyes costs 4 less to cast if a creature died this turn.
Create five 1/1 white Bat Cat creature tokens with flying.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Curse of Lightning</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>2R</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>You may sacrifice three permanents rather than pay Curse of Lightning’s mana cost.
Curse of Lightning deals 3 damage divided as you choose among one, two, or three targets.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Eve of the Promised End</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice a creature: Add R.
13, Sacrifice Eve of the Promised End: You control target player during that player’s next turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Kharadron Overlord</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>2R</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Dwarf Artificer </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever Kharadron Overlord enters or attacks, create two Junk tokens. (They’re artifacts with “T, Sacrifice this artifact: Exile the top card of your library. You may play that card this turn. Activate only as a sorcery.”)
Tap two untapped artifact you control: Put a +1/+1 counter on Kharadron Overlord, then it deals 1 damage to target player.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Xambriava, Vengeful Oracle</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>3B</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Gorgon Wizard </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Xambriava, Vengeful Oracle enters, you may return up to one target permanent card from your graveyard to the battlefield. You get a monarchy counter.
Creatures you control that are attacking the player with the most monarchy counters get +3/+0.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Kezah, the Squandered</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>W</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Creature - Spirit </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Hexproof
Whenever you sacrifice Kezah, the Squandered as part of the cost of a spell or ability you control, copy that spell or ability three times. You may choose new targets for the copies.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Clockwork Tower</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>3</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Scry 2.
Whenever you cast a spell, you may tap or untap up to one target nonland permanent.
4: Turbocharge. (Each other artifact you control has all activated and triggered abilities of this artifact until end of turn. Sacrifice this artifact at the beginning of the next end step.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Harbinger, Playful Enigma</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Creature - Horror </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>At the beginning of your upkeep, target opponent searches your library for a card, exiles that card face down, then shuffles. You choose two card names, then turn the exiled card face up. If it is a land or has one of the chosen names, put it into your hand, then search your library for any number of cards with the chosen names, reveal them, put them into your hand, then shuffle. Otherwise, put the exiled card into your hand.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Paradox Factory</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Tap two untapped artifacts you control: Draw a card.
Whenever Paradox Factory or another artifact you control enters, you may return an artifact you control with lesser mana value to its owner’s hand.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Fathom Corsair</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Human Artificer Pirate </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Squad 1
Islandwalk
Tap two untapped artifacts and/or Artificers you control: Plunder target opponent for 1. (Look at the top card of target opponent’s library. You may exile it face down. If you do, you may play that card using mana of any color for as long as it remains exiled.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Hrokvanar, the Devourer</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>RRRR</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Snow Creature - Wolf Demon </type>
 <pt>4/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Debauchery — This spell costs R less to cast for each card you’ve discarded this turn.
First strike, haste, menace
Whenever Hrokvanar, the Devourer deals combat damage to a player, exile that many cards from the top of your library. Until the end of your next turn, you may play those cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Kaliva, the Liberator</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>RR</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - God </type>
 <pt>4/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Haste
If a source would deal damage to Kaliva, the Liberator, prevent that damage. Discard cards equal to the damage prevented this way. 
Whenever you have no cards in hand, shuffle Kaliva, the Liberator into its owner’s library, then draw four cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Regrowth of Dragonfire</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>RG</color>
 <manacost>RG</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever a player discards a land card, you may put that card onto the battlefield under your control with a blaze counter on it. For as long as that land has a blaze counter on it, it has “At the beginning of your upkeep, this land deals 1 damage to you.”</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Teyaxoch, Hero of Orazca</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>2G</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Merfolk Warrior </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Teyaxoch, Hero of Orazca enters or attacks, you may search your library for a land card, reveal it, put it into your hand, then shuffle.
Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, scry 1, then you may manifest the top card of your library.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Pyramid Guardian</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Jackal Cleric </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Pyramid Guardian enters, each player sacrifices a creature.
Embalm 1B (1B, Exile this card from your graveyard: Create a token that’s a copy of it, except it’s a white Zombie Jackal Cleric with no mana cost. Embalm only as a sorcery.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Crown of the Conqueror</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Crown of the Conqueror enters the battlefield, target player gets a monarchy counter.
Whenever the player with the most monarchy counters draws a card, they lose 1 life.
Sacrifice a creature: Target opponent gets a monarchy counter and you lose a monarchy counter.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vampire Banquet</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Destroy target nonartifact creature. Each player creates X Blood tokens, where X is that creature’s power. (They’re artifacts with “1, T, Discard a card, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a card.”)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Granny Lovett</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Demon </type>
 <pt>0/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice a creature: Create a Food token.
T: Target opponent gains control of target Food you control. Create a Treasure token. You gain 1 life.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Bazaar Racketeer</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Cat Advisor Pirate </type>
 <pt>3/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever an opponent draws a card except for the first one they draw in each of their draw steps, that player puts a card from their hand on top of their library, then you plunder that opponent for 1. (Look at the top card of target opponent’s library. You may exile it face down. If you do, you may play that card using mana of any color for as long as it remains exiled.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Omenquoth</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Spirit Bird </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
When Omenquoth dies, search your library for a card, put that card into your hand, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Lich Priest Archfiend</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Lich Wizard Nightmare </type>
 <pt>1/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
When Lich Priest Archfiend deals combat damage to a player, you and that player each draw that many cards.
Whenever an opponent draws a card, put a +1/+1 counter on Lich Priest Archfiend.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Sekhmet Ritual</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>2BB</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>You may sacrifice four Blood artifacts rather than pay Sekhmet Ritual’s mana cost.
Each player discards their hand, then draws a card for each card in their graveyard.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Brass Marauder</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Construct Pirate </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Brass Marauder enters, choose one —
• Brass Marauder deals 2 damage to any target.
• Create two Treasure tokens.
• Plunder target opponent for 2.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Flight of Revelations</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Kicker 1B
When Flight of Revelations enters, if it was kicked, create four 1/1 black Skeleton creature tokens.
Skeleton creatures you control have horsemanship.
Sacrifice a creature: Target creature becomes a Skeleton in addition to its other types until end of turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Kinkiba, Who Coils The Leash</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>2B</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Snake Advisor </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Kinkiba, Who Coils The Leash enters, target player gets a monarchy counter.
Tap an untapped Advisor you control: Target player may exile a card from their hand. If they do, it becomes plotted, and that player draws a card at the beginning of the next end step. (They may cast it as a sorcery on a later turn without paying its mana cost.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Black Book of Hermaeus Mora</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>UBG</color>
 <manacost>BGU</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Cards in your graveyard have dredge 3. (If you would draw a card, you mill three cards instead. If you do, return this card from your graveyard to your hand. Otherwise, draw a card.)
Cumulative upkeep—Draw a card, then discard a card. (At the beginning of your upkeep, put an age counter on this permanent, then sacrifice it unless you pay its upkeep cost for each age counter on it.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Moonlight Biome</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Forest </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>(T: Add G.)
You may have Moonlight Biome enter as a copy of any land on the battlefield or in a graveyard, except it’s still a Forest in addition to its other types.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Reclamation of Zendikar</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>2G</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, create a 0/1 green Plant creature token, then each Plant you control explores. (Reveal the top card of your library. Put that card into your hand if it’s a land. Otherwise, put a +1/+1 counter on that creature, then put the card back or put it into your graveyard.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Catpurse Chicanery</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>You may return a roguish creature you control to its owner’s hand rather than pay this spell’s mana cost. (Faeries, Ninjas, Pirates, and Rogues are roguish.)
Counter target spell unless its controller pays 3. If a spell is countered this way, create X Treasure tokens, where X is that spell’s mana value.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Moonshadow Freebooter</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>2U</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Ninja Pirate </type>
 <pt>3/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
You may cast Roguish spells as though they had flash. (Faeries, Ninjas, Pirates, and Rogues are roguish.)
Tap an untapped roguish creature you control: Counter target spell unless its controller pays 1.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Parley</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Kindred Enchantment - Pirate </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever a player casts a spell from their hand, sacrifice Parley. If you do, each of that player’s opponents may plunder that player for 4. (Look at the top four cards of that player’s library. You may exile them face down. If you do, you may play those cards using mana of any color for as long as they remain exiled.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Landlubber's Demise</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>2U</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Kindred Sorcery - Pirate </type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Each player shuffles their hand and graveyard into their library, then draws seven cards. 
You may discard any number of land cards. If you do, plunder target opponent for X, where X is twice the number of cards discarded this way.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Rogue's Abyss</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add U, B, or R.
Whenever one or more roguish creatures you control deal combat damage to a player, create a Treasure token. (Faeries, Ninjas, Pirates, and Rogues are roguish.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Titan Skull Shrine</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add B or G.
1BG, T: Return target creature card from your graveyard to the battlefield. It’s a black Zombie in addition to its other colors and types, and it gains haste and decayed. (It can’t block. When it attacks, sacrifice it at end of combat.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Call the Deep Ones</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Escalate—Sacrifice a creature. (Pay this cost for each mode chosen beyond the first.)
Choose one or more —
• Target creature gets -2/-2 until end of turn.
• Return target creature card from your graveyard to your hand.
• Target player reveals their hand. You choose a creature card from it. That player discards that card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Infernal Council</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever an opponent draws a card, create a 1/1 black Demon Advisor creature token.
Whenever an opponent casts a spell, target Demon or Advisor creature you control connives.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Geist Shark Raid</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Destroy target creature, planeswalker, enchantment, or nonbasic land. Create a Treasure token.
Skirmish — If an opponent controls a spell and you control a Swamp, you may pay 4 life rather than pay Geist Shark Raid’s mana cost.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Lai Feng, Empress of Whispers</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Advisor </type>
 <pt>1/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Opponents reveal each card they draw.
Reconnaissance — Whenever an opponent reveals one or more cards, for each card revealed —
• If it’s a creature card, create a Food token.
• If it’s a land card, create a Treasure token.
• If it’s a noncreature, nonland card, create a Clue token.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Nullifying Lichcraft</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>As an additional cost to cast Nullifying Lichcraft, pay half your life rounded up.
Counter target spell. Put a lifelink counter on up to one target creature you control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Fastidious Dungeoneer</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>W</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Dwarf Artificer </type>
 <pt>1/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Fastidious Dungeoneer enters, take the initiative.
At the beginning of each end step, investigate X times, where X is the number of rooms you’ve entered this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Melsalin Gates</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add W, U, or B.
T: Exile target nonland permanent you control.
Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, you may return all permanent cards exiled by The Melsalin Gates to the battlefield under your control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Sunkissed Dreamscape</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Plains </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>(T: Add W.)
When Sunkissed Dreamscape enters, choose a color.
T: Add one mana of the chosen color.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Gloomcap Dreamscape</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Swamp </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>(T: Add B.)
When Gloomcap Dreamscape enters, choose a color.
T: Add one mana of the chosen color.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Windcliff Dreamscape</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Mountain </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>(T: Add R.)
When Windcliff Dreamscape enters, choose a color.
T: Add one mana of the chosen color.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Riverfall Dreamscape</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Island </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>(T: Add U.)
When Riverfall Dreamscape enters, choose a color.
T: Add one mana of the chosen color.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Rootroof Dreamscape</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Forest </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>(T: Add G.)
When Rootroof Dreamscape enters, choose a color.
T: Add one mana of the chosen color.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Footpath Dreamscape</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add C.
T, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Footpath Dreamscape:  Choose one —
• Search your library for a legendary land card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.
• Return target legendary land card from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Northern Terminus</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Snow Artifact Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add C.
Avalanche — T: For each land that’s entered the battlefield under your control this turn, add one mana of any color. Activate this ability only if a legendary land you control entered this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Explosive Fireflow</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add C.
T, Sacrifice Explosive Fireflow: Destroy target land. You and that land’s controller both reveal cards from the top of your library until you reveal a land card. Put those cards onto the battlefield and put all other cards revealed this way on the bottom of their owner’s libraries in a random order.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Timber Shiverer</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1BB</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Zombie Pirate </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Timber Shiverer enters, plunder target opponent for 2. (Look at the top two cards of target opponent’s library. You may exile them face down. If you do, you may play those cards using mana of any color for as long as they remain exiled.)
Whenever you plunder a player for X, up to one target creature that player controls gets -X/-X until end of turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Dreadship Raider</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Pirate </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>If it’s neither day nor night, it becomes night as Dreadship Raider enters.
Whenever it becomes night, put a +1/+1 counter on Dreadship Raider and plunder target opponent for 1.
As long as it’s night, Dreadship Raider is a Skeleton in addition to its other types and has menace.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Dashing Swashbuckler</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Pirate </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Deathtouch
When Dashing Swashbuckler enters, plunder target opponent for 2. (Look at the top two cards of target opponent’s library. You may exile them face down. If you do, you may play those cards using mana of any color for as long as they remain exiled.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Chumseeker</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Shark Pirate </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Intimidate (This creature can’t be blocked except by artifact creatures and/or creatures that share a color with it.)
Whenever Chumseeker deals combat damage to a player, plunder target opponent for 1. (Look at the top card of target opponent’s library. You may exile it face down. If you do, you may play that card using mana of any color for as long as it remains exiled.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Final Desolation</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>3BBB</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Each player discards their hand, then returns all creature cards from their graveyard to the battlefield. All creatures gain haste until end of turn. At the beginning of your next upkeep, each player sacrifices all creatures they control, then draws a card for each creature card in their graveyard.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mistress of Blades</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Phyrexian Horror </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Mistress of Blades enters, target player discards a card.
Phylactery (When this creature enters the battlefield, put a phylactery counter on up to one target artifact you control. You may cast this card from your graveyard by sacrificing an artifact with a phylactery counter on it in addition to paying its other costs.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Charge the Void</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice any number of permanents. For each permanent sacrificed this way, lose 1 life and exile the top card of your library. Until end of turn, you may play cards exiled this way.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Gubaraka, Quiet Awakener</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Spirit </type>
 <pt>0/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>You may play an additional land on each of your turns from your graveyard.
G, T: Search your library for a land card, put that card into your graveyard, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Captain Bane, Ghost of Dragaz</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Pirate Horror </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Deathtouch
Other Pirate creatures you control get +1/+1 and have deathtouch.
Whenever a creature an opponent owns dies, create a Treasure token and plunder that opponent for 1.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mystic Waygate</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Mystic Waygate enters, enter any room of any dungeon that’s not a final room or a room you’re currently in.
Whenever you complete a dungeon, look at the top X cards of your library, where X is the number of rooms in that dungeon. Put one of them into your hand and the rest on the bottom of your library in any order.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Treacherous Portal</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: You may put a permanent card from your hand or graveyard onto the battlefield. If you do, target opponent gains control of Treacherous Portal. Activate only as a sorcery.
Cycling 1 (1, Discard this card: Draw a card.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Hedron Animus</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Construct </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add one mana of any color. Take the initiative.
As long as you’ve fulfilled a prophecy, Hedron Animus gets +5/+5 and has flying, vigilance, and lifelink.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Loot Dimension</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When The Loot Dimension enters, scry 2, then draw a card.
Whenever you complete a dungeon, create a Treasure token for each different room you entered in that dungeon.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Caen Aiqua, the Forest of Tales</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add G.
T: Add G equal to the number of different rooms you’ve entered in the current dungeon.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Hermit Hideaway</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Forest Island </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>You may have Hermit Hideaway enter tapped. When you do, scry 3.
(T: Add G or U.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mindresdorth, Dragon Realm</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add R.
T: Add R for each spell you’ve cast this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ashengroth, Land of Nightmares</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add B.
T: Add B for each permanent card put into your graveyard from the battlefield this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Grand Imperial Museum</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add U, R, or W.
URW, T: Search your library for an artifact card, reveal it, put it into your hand, then shuffle</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Wrath of the Sea God</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill Wrath of the Sea God as a sorcery if seven or more lands have entered the battlefield under your control this turn. When you do, return all nonland permanents you don’t control to their owner’s hands.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Um Osri, the World of Ideas</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add U.
T: Add U for each card you’ve drawn this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Rune of Terror</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Replicate—Tap an untapped Artificer or Wizard you control. (When you cast this spell, copy it for each time you paid its replicate cost. You may choose new targets for the copies.)
Scry 2.
Create a Rune Trap artifact token with “T, Sacrifice this artifact: Counter target spell unless its controller pays 2.”</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Biolight Presence</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Elemental </type>
 <pt>1/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
When Biolight Presence enters the battlefield, untap all permanents you control.
Whenever you complete a dungeon, creatures you control get +1/+1 and gain trample until end of turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Krosan Dragon</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>2G</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Plant Dragon </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
Reach, haste
As long as Krosan Dragon is on the battlefield, it is a land in addition to its other types and has all abilities of all land cards in your graveyard.
Dredge 3</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Avatar of Journeys</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WBG</color>
 <manacost>WBG</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Spirit Avatar </type>
 <pt>5/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Lifelink
Whenever another permanent you control is put into your graveyard from the battlefield, if Avatar of Journeys is on the battlefield or in your graveyard, venture into the dungeon.
Whenever you complete a dungeon, you may return Avatar of Journeys from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Boss Monster Hydra</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Hydra </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Trample
Whenever you cast an Adventure spell or venture into the dungeon, put a +1/+1 counter on Boss Monster Hydra. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
When Boss Monster Hydra dies, if you’ve completed a dungeon, create X Treasure tokens, where X is its power.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Fall of the Empire</name>
 <set rarity="mythic" splitterPath="/Fall of the Empire.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color>WB</color>
 <related attach="attach">Runivar, the Despot</related>
 <manacost>WB</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment - Saga </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>
---
(Back): Runivar, the Despot</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Runivar, the Despot</name>
 <set rarity="mythic" splitterPath="/Runivar, the Despot.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color>WB</color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Knight </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Afflict 3 (Whenever that creature becomes blocked, defending player loses 3 life.)
Whenever an opponent takes the initiative, that player sacrifices a permanent.
Whenever an opponent gets a monarchy counter, create a Treasure token.
---
(Front): Fall of the Empire</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ugualag, Storm Conduit</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>UG</color>
 <manacost>GU</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Cyclops Wizard </type>
 <pt>1/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Ugualag, Storm Conduit enters, scry 3.
Magecraft — Whenever you cast or copy an instant or sorcery spell, you may put a land card from your hand onto the battlefield. If you don’t, you may scry 3.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Experience Infinity</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>UU</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Target player draws a card.
Storm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each spell cast before it this turn. You may choose new targets for the copies.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Sukani's Treason</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Divination — Until end of turn, each time you look at cards from the top of a library, you may exile one of those cards. If you do, it becomes plotted. (You may cast it as a sorcery on a later turn without paying its mana cost.)
Scry 4.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Dissection Ritual</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>XU</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Delve (Each card you exile from your graveyard while casting this spell pays for 1.)
Scry X, the create X Blood tokens. (To scry X, look at the top X cards of your library, then put any number of them on the bottom of your library and the rest on top in any order.)
Until end of turn, activated abilities of artifacts you control cost 2 less to activate.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Summon Through Time</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Search your library for a nonland card and exile it, then shuffle. Put X time counters on it, where X is its mana value. If it doesn’t have suspend, it gains suspend.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ancestral Gambit</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Choose a card name, then look at the top card of your library. If that card has the chosen name, you may reveal it and draw four cards. Otherwise, you may draw a card.
Flashback 2U (You may cast this card from your graveyard for its flashback cost. Then exile it.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Premonition Engine</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Divination — Whenever you look at cards from the top of a library, you may discover X, where X is the number of cards looked at this way. (Exile cards from the top of your library until you exile a nonland cards with mana value X or less. Cast it without paying its mana cost or put it into your hand. Put the rest on the bottom in a random order.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Shallan, the Lightweaver</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WG</color>
 <manacost>GW</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Wizard </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>T: You may venture into the dungeon, then you may search your library for a creature card with mana value equal to the number of different rooms you’ve entered in the current dungeon, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Sundered Horizon</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>UG</color>
 <manacost>1GU</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
When Sundered Horizon enters, you may search your library for a land card, put it onto the battlefield tapped, then shuffle.
Return a land you control to its owner’s hand: Add one mana of any color.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Live Long</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>2G // 2G</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery // Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Search your library for up to three land cards, reveal them, put them into your hand, then shuffle.
You gain 3 life.
--- 
Put any number of land cards from your hand onto the battlefield, then draw that many cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Captain's Command</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>XU</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Choose one —
• Gain control of target spell with mana value X or less. You may choose new targets for it.
• Create X Treasure tokens.
• Plunder target opponent for X. (Look at the top X cards of target opponent’s library. You may exile them face down. If you do, you may play those cards using mana of any color for as long as they remain exiled.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Dark One's Prison</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When The Dark One’s Prison enters, exile your graveyard face down.
If a card would be put into your graveyard from anywhere, instead exile that card face down.
T: Surveil 1, then manifest a face-down card you own in exile.
When The Dark One’s Prison leaves the battlefield, put any number of face-down cards you own in exile into your graveyard.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Cemetery Waltz</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>BG</color>
 <manacost>BG</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Return target creature card from your graveyard to the battlefield. That creature is a black Zombie in addition to its other colors and types, and it gains decayed.
Dredge 2</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Prex, Radical Prodigy</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Artificer </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>T: Discard a card, then draw a card.
Whenever an artifact card is put into your graveyard from anywhere other than the battlefield, you may exile it. If you do, you may play that card until the end of your next turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Technocherub</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>WU</color>
 <manacost>4WU</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Angel </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying, hexproof
When Technocherub enters, search your library for an artifact card, reveal it, put it into your hand, then shuffle.
When Technocherub leaves the battlefield, tap up to six target permanents. Put a stun counter on each of those permanents.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ra'Talai, of the Sunken City</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Merfolk Artificer </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Ra’Talai, of the Sunken City enters, search your library for an artifact card, reveal it, put it into your hand, then shuffle.
Whenever you cast an instant or sorcery spell, you may sacrifice an artifact. If you do, copy that spell. You may choose new targets for the copy.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Dreamwood Forager</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Insect Construct </type>
 <pt>0/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
Inspired — When Dreamwood Forager becomes untapped, choose one — 
• Create two Treasure tokens.
• Draw a card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Open The Eyes of the World</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>RG</color>
 <manacost>RG</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Until end of turn, whenever you cast a spell, you may create a token that’s a copy of target land you control and exile the top card of your library. You may play that card this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Saoirse, Relic Thief</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>UR</color>
 <manacost>UR</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Rogue </type>
 <pt>1/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Saoirse, Relic Thief can’t be blocked.
Prowess (Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, this creature gets +1/+1 until end of turn.)
Historic spells you cast cost X less to cast, where X is Saoirse, Relic Thief’s power. (Artifacts, legendaries, and Sagas are historic.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Headless Headtaker</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>WB</color>
 <manacost>1WB</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Nightmare </type>
 <pt>4/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
First strike
When Headless Headtaker enters, destroy target creature.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Astral Archer</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Spirit </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Reach
T: Venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
As long as you’ve fulfilled a prophecy, creatures you control get +3/+3 and have haste.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Curious Dreamship</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact - Vehicle </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
Whenever Curious Dreamship attacks, exile all creatures crewing it, then create a token copy of each of those creatures.
When Curious Dreamship leaves the battlefield, return all creatures exiled by it to the battlefield under their owner’s control.
Crew 1</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Joqi, Dreamspace Guide</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Spirit </type>
 <pt>1/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever Joqi, Dreamspace Guide or another creature you control enters, venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
Room abilities of dungeons you own trigger an additional time for each different dungeon you’ve completed.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Naesasia, The Sunlit Frost</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Snow Creature - Centaur </type>
 <pt>1/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>T: Scry 1.
Divination — Whenever you look at cards from the top of a library, create X 1/1 blue Bird creature tokens, where X is the number of cards looked at this way.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Tainted Lotus</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>0</manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>At the beginning of your upkeep, you get a poison counter.
T, Sacrifice Tainted Lotus: You get a poison counter, then add one mana of any color for each poison counter you have.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Zachiel, the First Reaper</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>M</color>
 <manacost>1W // B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Spirit  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Other nontoken creatures you control have afterlife 1. (Whenever this creature dies, create a 1/1 white and black Spirit creature token with flying.)
--- 
Search your library for a card, put that card into your graveyard, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Halimari Diversion</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Until the end of your next turn, you may fulfill unfulfilled prophecies owned by your opponents.
Scry 2, then draw a card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Birthing Spire</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>4H/GH/G</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T, Sacrifice Birthing Spire: Sacrifice any number of creatures you control. For each creature sacrificed this way, search your library for a creature card with mana value equal to 1 plus the sacrificed creature’s mana value, put that card onto the battlefield. Then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Winterwind Apprentice</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>W // W</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Bird Monk Wizard  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
When Winterwind Apprentice enters, take the initiative.
--- 
Exile target permanent you control, then return it to the battlefield under its owner’s control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Nakai, Ancient Teacher</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>WG</color>
 <manacost>1GW</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Bird </type>
 <pt>3/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
When Nakai, Ancient Teacher enters, search your library for creature card with base power and toughness 1/1, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle. Put a training counter on that creature. (Whenever that creature attacks with another creature with greater power, put a +1/+1 counter on that creature.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Jade River Hunter</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Warrior </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever Jade River Hunter attacks, you may discover X, where X is the number of rooms you’ve entered this turn. If you haven’t entered any rooms this turn, take the initiative instead.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Alignment of the Spheres</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>At the beginning of your upkeep, you may fulfill The Alignment of the Spheres if you control five nonland permanents with consecutive mana values. When you do, return up to five target permanents to their owner’s hands, then draw five cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Harmony's End</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill Harmony’s End at the beginning of your upkeep after your third turn of the game if each player controls the same number of permanents. When you do, create Marit Lage, a legendary 20/20 black Avatar creature token with flying and indestructible.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Shimmering Tomorrow</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>2U</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Take an extra turn after this one. If W was spent to cast this spell, creatures you control have first strike, during that turn. The same is true for B and menace, R and haste, and G and trample, respectively.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Blossom, the Impending Fang</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Snow Creature - Goat Warrior </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>At the beginning of you upkeep, scry X, where X is the number of creatures you control.
If one or more tokens would be created under your control, those tokens plus that many additional 4/4 black Wolf Demon snow creature tokens are created instead.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Meletis Artisan</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>4U</manacost>
 <cmc>5</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Sphinx Artificer </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Affinity for artifacts (This spell costs 1 less to cast for each artifact you control.)
Flying
Whenever you cast an nonartifact spell, you may pay U. If you do, create a token that’s a copy of target artifact you control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Protean Titan</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>7</manacost>
 <cmc>7</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Construct </type>
 <pt>6/6</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Protean Titan leaves the battlefield, search your library for any number of artifact cards with total mana value 6 or less, put them onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vengeful Archfiend</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>6</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Construct Horror </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Haunt (When this creature dies, exile it haunting target creature.)
When Vengeful Archfiend enters the battlefield or the creature it haunts dies, each opponent discards three cards and loses 3 life. You draw three cards and gain 3 life.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Ultimate Ascension</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill The Ultimate Ascension at the beginning of the end step if you have 15 or more cards in your hand. When you do, untap all lands you control. You get an emblem with “You have no maximum hand size” and “You may cast spells as though they had flash.”</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Starfall, the Avaricious</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>10</manacost>
 <cmc>10</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Creature - Angel </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Affinity for tokens (This spell costs 1 less to cast for each token you control.)
When Starfall, the Avaricious enters or leaves the battlefield, gain control of target permanent.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vagrdrifa, Soul of the Sword</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>M</color>
 <manacost>4RW</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Valkyrie God  // Legendary Artifact</type>
 <pt>5/5</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying, first strike, vigilance, haste, protection from artifacts. (This creature can’t be blocked, targeted, dealt damage, or equipped by artifacts.)
R: Transform Vagrdrifa, Soul of the Sword.
--- 
When this permanent transforms into Banamaðr, it deals 3 damage to any target and you gain 3 life.
W: Transform Banamaðr.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Azure Clepsydra</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>10</manacost>
 <cmc>10</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Affinity for artifacts (This spell costs 1 less to cast for each artifact you control.)
When Azure Clepsydra enters the battlefield, you gain 5 life and draw five cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Eikthyrnir, the Blood Harvest</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>BG</color>
 <manacost>BG</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Deer God </type>
 <pt>5/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>As an additional cost to cast Eikthyrnir, the Blood Harvest, sacrifice two lands.
Deathtouch, trample
Sacrifice a creature: Return up to one target land card from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Necrotic Wind</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>BG</color>
 <manacost>BG</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Destroy target nonbasic permanent. You gain life equal to its mana value.
Fertilize (When this card is put into your graveyard from your hand or library, you may return up to one target land card from your graveyard to the battlefield.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vircek Slimewalker</name>
 <set rarity="common">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Vircek </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>T: Venture into the dungeon, then you may mill two cards. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
Viral 2 (Whenever this card is put into your graveyard from anywhere, mill two cards.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Lichenous Oracle</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Fungus Wizard </type>
 <pt>0/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Tap an untapped Fungus or Wizard you control: Venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
If you would draw a card while your library has no cards in it, instead create a token that’s a copy of Lichenous Oracle. (Whenever you draw a card, this ability triggers once for this creature and each of the copies.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Hydrosphere</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Look at the top two cards of target player’s library.
Sacrifice an artifact or creature: Target player mills two cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Gods Take Notice</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill The Gods Take Notice as an instant whenever you complete your second dungeon. When you do, search your library for a permanent card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Frostlance Barrage</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>URG</color>
 <manacost>1GUR</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Snow Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Avalanche — Sacrifice any number of lands, draw that many cards, then you may put any number of land cards from your hand onto the battlefield. Frostlance Barrage deals X damage to each opponent and each creature they  control, where X is the number of lands that entered under your control this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Devouring Graveminds</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>2RR</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Each player discards their hand, draws seven cards, then creates X 1/1 red Vircek Horror creature tokens, where X is the number of noncreature cards in their graveyard.
Madness 1R (If you discard this card, discard it into exile. When you do, cast it for its madness cost or put it into your graveyard.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Jan Sul, Mirran Guardian</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>4</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Creature - Construct </type>
 <pt>4/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice an artifact: Draw a card.
Artifact and enchantment creature cards in your graveyard have legacy 1R/W. (1R/W, Exile this card from your graveyard: Create a token that’s a copy of it, except it’s not a creature. Activate only as a sorcery.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Sitting Idol</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Golem </type>
 <pt>4/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Sitting Idol enters tapped and doesn’t untap during its controller’s untap step.
Inspired — When Sitting Idol becomes untapped, create four Treasure tokens. (They’re artifacts with “T, Sacrifice this artifact: Add one mana of any color.”)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Crashing Herald</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>2G</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Elemental </type>
 <pt>4/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Trample
R: Creatures you control gain haste until end of turn.
Whenever Crashing Herald deals combat damage to a player, you may sacrifice any number of lands. If you do, search your library for up to that many land cards, put them onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>A Dream of Spring</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Snow Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Search your library for a land card, put that card onto the battlefield, then shuffle. If that land is snow or legendary, scry 2.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Umaule, Elder Oneiromancer</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1UU</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Merfolk Wizard </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
When Umaule, Elder Oneiromancer enters the battlefield, you may cast target instant or sorcery card from your graveyard without paying its mana cost. If you do, exile it as it resolves.
Whenever you fulfill a prophecy, you may take an extra turn after this one.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Lake of Fallen Blades</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Snow Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add R or G.
Imprint — Whenever a creature you control dies, you exile an artifact card from your graveyard.
When The Lake of Fallen Blades is put into a graveyard from the battlefield, until the end of your next turn, you may play the imprinted cards from exile.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Chaos Nexus</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever you cast a spell, create X 0/1 black and red Chaos Spawn artifact creature tokens, where X is that spell’s mana value.
Whenever an opponent casts a spell, each Chaos Spawn creature you control deals 1 damage to you.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Frozen Chain Temple</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add B.
T, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Frozen Chain Temple: Search your library for a Island or Mountain card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Where Blood Flows as Lava</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add B, R, or G.
Pay 1 life, Sacrifice a creature: Return Where Blood Flows as Lava from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Oathbeacon Temple</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add W.
T, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Oathbeacon Temple: Search your library for a Forest or Island card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Verdant Sky Temple</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add G.
T, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Verdant Sky Temple: Search your library for an Mountain or Plains card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Loral's Sanctuary</name>
 <set rarity="mythic" splitterPath="/Loral's Sanctuary.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <related attach="attach">Loral's Final Battle</related>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add W, B, or G.
Whenever you complete a dungeon, you may exile Loral’s Sanctuary, then return it to the battlefield transformed under its owner’s control.
---
(Back): Loral's Final Battle</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Loral's Final Battle</name>
 <set rarity="mythic" splitterPath="/Loral's Final Battle.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Enchantment - Saga </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>
I — Create Loral, a legendary 4/4 colorless Construct artifact creature token.
II, III — Loral gets +1/+1 for each creature you control until end of turn, then it fights each creature your opponents control.
You gain 1 life for each creature you control.
---
(Front): Loral's Sanctuary</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Vestigial Rifts</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add G, U, or R.
Channel — GUR, Discard The Vestigial Rifts: The next spell you cast from your hand this turn gains cascade. (When you cast that spell, exile cards from the top of your library until you exile a nonland card that costs less. You may cast it without paying its mana cost. Put the exiled cards on the bottom in a random order.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Bankai, City of Dark Beasts</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add B, G, or U.
BGU, T, Sacrifice Bankai, City of Dark Beasts: Return target card from your graveyard to your hand.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Sound Beast Storm</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>2G</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice a land: Venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
Whenever you complete a dungeon, create a 5/5 green Beast creature token with trample and haste.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Piranai, The Blighted Bloom</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>BG</color>
 <manacost>B/G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Dryad </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Pay 1 life: Put up to one land card from your hand onto the battlefield with a blight counter on it.
T, Remove a blight counter from target land you control: Put a -1/-1 counter on target creature.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Fun Gus, Rot Farmer</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>2G</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Fungus </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Tap an untapped creature you control: Exile target card from a graveyard.
Whenever another creature you control dies, reveal cards from the top of your library until you reveal a land card. Put that card onto the battlefield and the rest on the bottom of your library in a random order.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Yang-Light Moon</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land // Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add W. Flip Yang-Light Moon.
--- 
T: Add B. Flip Yin-Dark Moon.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Search the Spirit Realm</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Draw three cards, then put two cards from your hand on top of your library in any order. 
If you’ve fulfilled a prophecy, create a 1/1 blue Spirit creature token for each card you’ve drawn this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Relic Hunter</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Werewolf Rogue </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>T: Venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
G, Sacrifice Relic Hunter: Destroy target artifact or enchantment.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Deepwood Ritualist</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Dryad Shaman </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Trample
Sacrifice a creature: Venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
Unearth G (G: Return this card from your graveyard to the battlefield. It gains haste. Exile it at the beginning of the end step or if it would leave the battlefield. Unearth only as a sorcery.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Affluent Patron</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W // 1W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Vampire Noble  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice a creature: Venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
--- 
Create two 1/1 white Human Mercenary Warrior creature tokens.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Trap Hole</name>
 <set rarity="common">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add 1.
Whenever a creature comes into play, sacrifice Trap Hole and bury that creature.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Xenthil, Gleaming Destiny</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>6WW</manacost>
 <cmc>8</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Creature - Dragon </type>
 <pt>5/5</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
When Xenthil, Gleaming Destiny enters, each player sacrifices X nonartifact permanents, where X is the number of artifacts you control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Epic Adventure</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>RG</color>
 <manacost>RG</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
Storm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each spell cast before it this turn.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Expunge the Unholy</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>W</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Destroy target artifact, enchantment, or planeswalker.
Cycling W (W, Discard this card: Draw a card.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mycelium Perimeter</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may play land cards from your graveyard.
Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, you may create a 2/2 green Fungus Warrior creature token.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Alumaku Caravan</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Snow Creature - Human Nomad </type>
 <pt>1/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Alumaku Caravan enters the battlefield, mill four cards.
Whenever a land card is put into your graveyard from anywhere, create a Treasure token.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Doomwheel</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>4</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Artifact - Vehicle </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Haste, trample
Sacrifice an artifact or creature: Add two mana of any color.
Whenever you sacrifice your fifth artifact or creature this turn, Doomwheel becomes an artifact creature until end of turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Lost Discus</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add CCW.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Code of the Hegemony</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>WU</color>
 <manacost>1WU</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Tap an untapped creature you control: Tap target permanent.
Tap an untapped artifact you control: Put a stun counter on target permanent.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mul Daya Seed Warden</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Spirit Druid </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Mul Daya Seed Warden enters, draw a card.
Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, you may return Mul Daya Seed Warden from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Kami of Sleepless Nights</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>BB</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Spirit </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Haste
Whenever Kami of Sleepless Nights or another card leaves your graveyard, create a 1/1 black Spirit creature token with haste.
Escape—Sacrifice two creatures and exile two cards from your graveyard. (You may cast this card from your graveyard for its escape cost.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ziggy the Odious</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>2R</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Devil </type>
 <pt>3/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>If a spell or ability you control would cause you to commit a crime, you may copy it and you may choose new targets for the copy. The copy cannot trigger this ability.
At the beginning of your end step, Ziggy the Odious deals X damage to target player, where X is the number of crimes you’ve committed this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Otherseeker</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Vircek </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Otherseeker enters, it fights target creature.
Dredge 5 (If you would draw a card, you mill five cards instead. If you do, return this card from your graveyard to your hand. Otherwise, draw a card.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mat'ergenu, Prophet of Ruin</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Vircek </type>
 <pt>6/6</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Trample, haste
When Mat’ergenu, Prophet of Ruin enters, sacrifice it unless you’re part of the hive. (You’re part of the hive when your library has at most half as many cards as it did at the start of the game.)
Dredge 6 (If you would draw a card, you mill six cards instead. If you do, return this card from your graveyard to your hand. Otherwise, draw a card.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Traverse the Precipice</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Cleave BRG  (You may cast this spell for its cleave cost. If you do, remove the words in square brackets.)
Return to the battlefield all permanent cards in your graveyard that were put there [from the battlefield] this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Fy'Alari, the Guiding</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature Land - Spirit </type>
 <pt>0/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Haste
T: Add G, W, or U.
Whenever you expand the frontier, up to one target creature you control explores. (You expand the frontier when a land you control enters that does not share a name with another land you control.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Skylark Streamsong</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W // W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Wizard  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>When Skylark Streamsong enters, venture into the dungeon X times, where X is the number of creatures you control. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
--- 
Until end of turn, whenever an opponent casts a spell, you may gain 1 life, draw a card and create a 1/1 white Spirit creature token with flying.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Munda, the Spider</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W // W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Kor Warrior  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>When Munda, the Spider enters, destroy up to one target creature with mana value 3 or greater.
--- 
Destroy target creature with mana value 3 or less.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Opening Encounter</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>W</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Take the initiative.
Destroy target nonland permanent with mana value three or less.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Emrakul, Who Shattered the Moon</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Eldrazi </type>
 <pt>13/13</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Suspend 13—1
Whenever a card is put into your graveyard from anywhere, remove a time counter from Emrakul, Who Shattered the Moon.
Flying, trample, annihilator 3
If Emrakul would be put into a graveyard from anywhere, exile Emrakul with thirteen time counters on it.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Kelsier, Survivor of Hathsin</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>BR</color>
 <manacost>1B/R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Allomancer </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice an artifact: Choose one —
• Kelsier gains flying and haste until end of turn.
• Kelsier gets +1/+1 until end of turn.
• Kelsier deals 1 damage to any target.
• Target player reveals their hand.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Obsidian Aurora</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment Artifact - Aura Curse </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Enchant player
At the beginning of enchanted player’s upkeep, you lose X life and create X 1/1 black Viseling artifact creature tokens, where X is the number of cards in enchanted player’s hand minus 4.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Infinity Key</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WUR</color>
 <manacost>URW</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When The Infinity Key is put into your graveyard from the battlefield, take an extra turn after this one. During that turn, players can’t attack or block with nonartifact creatures, or cast nonartifact spells. After that turn, you can’t take additional extra turns until an opponent takes a turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Twisting Sanity</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>XX1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Discard your hand, then draw that many cards plus one. Repeat this process X times.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Witching Hour</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WBR</color>
 <manacost>RWB</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Pay 1 life, Sacrifice a permanent: Return target card from your graveyard to your hand.
Discard a card: Add one mana of any color.
At the beginning of the end step, sacrifice The Witching Hour.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Intrusion of Oblivion</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>3R</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Cleave 4B (You may cast this spell for its cleave cost. If you do, remove the words in square brackets.)
Target player discards their hand [and draws seven cards].
Overload 2R (You may cast this spell for its overload cost. If you do, change its text by replacing all instances of “target” with “each”.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Lightning Infuser</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Wizard </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
You may cast artifact and sorcery spells as though they had flash.
Spells you cast that are artifact or sorcery spells during an opponent’s turn cost 2 less to cast.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Old Master Sarai</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>RG</color>
 <manacost>RG</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Bird Wizard </type>
 <pt>0/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
You may activate abilities of creatures you control as though those creatures had haste.
Magecraft — Whenever you cast or copy an instant or sorcery spell, create a 0/1 green Bird creature token with flying and “T: Add one mana of any color.”</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Enscribe the Future</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>If you’ve fulfilled a prophecy, scry 3, then draw 3 cards. Otherwise, scry 1, then draw a card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Stratosphere Surveyor</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Human Artificer </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
Whenever Stratosphere Surveyor or another artifact you control enters, you may draw a card. If you do, discard a card.
Legacy 1 (1, Exile this card from your graveyard: Create a token that’s a copy of it, except it’s not a creature. Activate only as a sorcery.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Echraverra's Vault</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Target player loses 1 life and you gain 1 life.
Sacrifice any number of permanents: Fateseal X, where X is the number of permanents sacrificed this way. (To fateseal X, look at the top X cards of an opponent’s library, then put any number of them on the bottom of that player’s library and the rest on top in any order.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vircek Incubation Pod</name>
 <set rarity="common">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice Vircek Incubation Pod: Draw two cards, then discard two cards.
Viral 2 (Whenever this card is put into your graveyard from anywhere, mill two cards.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Eldritch Flame</name>
 <set rarity="common">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Eldritch Flame deals 4 damage to target creature.
Dredge 4 (If you would draw a card, you mill four cards instead. If you do, return this card from your graveyard to your hand. Otherwise, draw a card.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Obcenasith, Prophet of Might</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>BG</color>
 <manacost>4BG</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Vircek </type>
 <pt>6/6</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Obcenasith, Prophet of Might costs X less to cast, where X is the number of cards put into your graveyard from anywhere this turn.
Trample, deathtouch, haste
You may cast Obcenasith, Prophet of Might from your graveyard if you’re part of the hive. (You’re part of the hive when your library has at most half as many cards as it did at the start of the game.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Dream Binder</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>4</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
When Dream Binder enters, exile up to one target spell.
When Dream Binder leaves the battlefield, you may cast the exiled card without paying its mana cost.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Phial of Acid</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Phial of Acid enters or leaves the battlefield, it deals 2 damage to any target.
1R, Sacrifice Phial of Acid: Reveal cards from the top of your library until you reveal an artifact card. Put that card into your hand and the rest on the bottom of your library in any order.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Shrike, Lord of Pain</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>3</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Creature - Construct </type>
 <pt>4/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>First strike, deathtouch
The Shrike, Lord of Pain can’t block.
1: Exile The Shrike.
2: Exile The Shrike from your graveyard.
3: Return The Shrike from exile to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Stuff the Scarecrows</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Create a 1/1 colorless Scarecrow artifact creature token.
Gravestorm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each permanent put into a graveyard this turn.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Whisper, the Nameless Fear</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WB</color>
 <manacost>WB</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Enchantment Creature - Nightmare </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
Bestow 2WB (If you cast this card for its bestow cost, it’s an Aura spell with enchant creature. It becomes a creature again if it’s not attached to a creature.)
Whenever Whisper, the Nameless Fear or enchanted creature deals combat damage to a player, each player sacrifices a nonland permanent or discards a card for each damage dealt.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Liege of the Torrent</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Spirit Wizard </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, scry 2.
Divination — Whenever you look at cards from the top of a library, target creature you control gets +X/+X and can’t be blocked this turn, where X is the number of cards you looked at this way.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Eureka Moment</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>At the beginning of your upkeep, you may fulfill The Eureka Moment if you cast three or more spells last turn. When you do, return all instant and sorcery cards from your graveyard to your hand. Until end of turn, instant and sorcery spells you cast cost 1 less to cast.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Daratrine, Questing Flame</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Elf Shaman </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever you expand the frontier, reveal cards from the top of your library until you reveal an instant or sorcery card. Put that card into your hand and the rest on the bottom of your library in a random order. (You expand the frontier when a land you control enters that does not share a name with another land you control.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Conquering the Shadow Realm</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>If you would draw a card while your library has no cards in it, instead fulfill The Conquering the Shadow Realm. When you do, create an emblem with “If you would draw a card while your library has no cards in it, instead you may put up to one target creature card from a graveyard onto the battlefield under your control.”</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Seat of Judgement</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>BBB</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T, Pay 7 life: Add BBBBBBB.
Sacrifice a God: Untap The Seat of Judgement. You gain life equal to the sacrificed God’s mana value.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Night-Eyes Totem</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Choose one — 
• Draw a card, then discard a card.
• Untap another target permanent.
Sacrifice a permanent: Untap Night-Eyes Totem. Activate this ability no more than twice each turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Slickskin Gladiator</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>2G // G</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Seal Warrior  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever you cast an Adventure spell or venture into the dungeon, Slickskin Gladiator fights up to one target creature.
--- 
Target creature you control fights target creature you don’t control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Protector of the Hive</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>M</color>
 <manacost>1G // 1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Insect Warrior  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
Whenever a creature you control becomes the target of a spell or ability an opponent controls, you may have target creature you control fight another target creature you don’t control.
--- 
Create two 1/1 green Insect creature tokens with flying and deathtouch.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Captain Saaqa Shankaron</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Merfolk Pirate </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Captain Saaqa Shankaron enters, gain control of target creature with mana value 3 or less until end of turn. Untap that creature. It gains haste until end of turn.
Dash 1R (You may cast this spell for its dash cost. If you do, it gains haste, and it’s returned from the battlefield to its owner’s hand at the beginning of the next end step.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Captain Greylock, the Undertow</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Pirate </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever you cast an instant or sorcery spell, gain control of up to one target nonland permanent until end of turn with mana value less than or equal to that of the instant or sorcery spell. Untap that permanent. It gains haste until end of turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Covert Demolition</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>XXR</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Destroy up to X target artifacts. Investigate twice X times. (Create a colorless Clue artifact token with “2, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a card.”)
Artifactcycling 1R (1R, Discard this card: Search your library for an Artifact card, reveal it, and put it into your hand, then shuffle.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Eruption Firebird</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>2RR</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Elemental Phoenix </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying, haste
Whenever a land card is put into a graveyard from anywhere, Eruption Firebird deals 2 damage to any target.
R, Sacrifice a legendary land: Return Eruption Firebird from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Yageki Storm Sage</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G // 1G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Bird Wizard  // Instant - Adventure </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>1: You may return target creature you control to its owner’s hand. If you do, target player mills cards equal to that creature’s power.
--- 
Put target noncreature permanent on top of its owner’s library.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Villainous Inception</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>2R</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Gain control of up to one target nonland permanent with mana value 3 or less until end of turn. Untap that permanent. It gains haste until end of turn.
Undercut (When you discard this card, return up to one target card with lesser mana value from your graveyard to your hand.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Quasar Geyser</name>
 <set rarity="common">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Quasar Geyser deals 3 damage to any target.
Viral 3 (Whenever this card is put into your graveyard from anywhere, mill three cards.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Realm-Spanning Battle</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>UR</color>
 <manacost>UR</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Realm-Spanning Battle enters, scry 2.
Divination — Whenever you look at cards from the top of a library, Realm-Spanning Battle deals X damage to any target, where X is the number of cards looked at this way.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Reckless Conclusions</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Escalate—Counter target spell you control. (Pay this cost for each mode chosen beyond the first.)
Choose one or more —
• Reckless Conclusions deals 3 damage to any target.
• Add three mana in any combination of colors.
• Exile the top three cards of your library. Until end of turn, you may play those cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Arcane Overload</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant - Arcane </type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Add URR.
Splice onto blue instant or sorcery 1R. (As you cast a blue instant or sorcery spell, you may reveal this card from your hand and pay its splice cost. If you do, add this card’s effects to that spell.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Unfold the Pattern</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>UR</color>
 <manacost>UR</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Draw three cards, then exile three cards from your hand. You may play the exiled cards this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Spiral</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>M</color>
 <manacost>U // B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant // Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Return target nonland permanent to its owner’s hand.
--- 
Aftermath (Cast this spell only from your graveyard, then exile it.)
Target player reveals their hand. You choose a nonland permanent card from it. That player discards that card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vampiric Piracy</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>UB</color>
 <manacost>UB</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Put up to one target spell or nonland permanent on top of its owner’s library, then plunder that player for 1. (Look at the top card of that player’s library. You may exile it face down. If you do, you may play that card using mana of any color for as long as it remains exiled.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Skekra, the Deceiver</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>5U</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Bird Wizard </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Skekra, the Deceiver costs 1 less to cast for each instant and sorcery card in your graveyard.
Flying
When Skekra, the Deceiver enters, surveil 3, then draw three cards. (Look at the top three cards of your library, then put any number of them into your graveyard and the rest on top of your library in any order.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>A New Hand Touches the Beacon</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Choose a prophecy you’ve fulfilled this game. You may fulfill it again.
Scry 1, then draw a card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Secure the Essentials</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Surveil 2 (Look at the top two cards of your library, then put any number of them into your graveyard and the rest on top of your library in any order.)
Draw a card.
You may search your library for a card named Bottle O’Rum, put it into your hand, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Graveshot</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Graveshot deals 1 damage to any target.
Gravestorm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each permanent put into a graveyard this turn. You may choose new targets for the copies.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Marauder's Sanctuary</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, plunder target opponent for 1. (Look at the top card of target opponent’s library. You may exile it face down. If you do, you may play that card using mana of any color for as long as it remains exiled.)
Whenever you play a card from exile, create a Treasure token.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Taelon Vama</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2WW</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Bird </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Rather than pay Taelon Vama’s mana cost, you may return any number of permanents you control to their owner’s hands with total mana value equal to four or greater.
Flash, flying
When Taelon Vama enters the battlefield, exile up to one target creature. Its controller gains life equal to its mana value.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Spirit of Ada</name>
 <set rarity="rare" splitterPath="/Spirit of Ada.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <related attach="attach">Spirit of Diwala</related>
 <manacost>2GG</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Elemental </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Lands you control are 1/1 green Elemental creatures in addition to their other colors and types.
3G: Create a token that’s a copy of target land you control. Transform Spirit of Ada.
---
(Back): Spirit of Diwala</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Spirit of Diwala</name>
 <set rarity="rare" splitterPath="/Spirit of Diwala.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>2GG</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Elemental </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Creatures you control are lands in addition to their other types.
3G: Create a token that’s a copy of target creature you control. Transform Spirit of Diwala.
---
(Front): Spirit of Ada</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mirage Oasis</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>For each land card in your graveyard, create a token that’s a copy of it. Sacrifice those tokens at the beginning of the next end step.
Miracle—U (You may cast this card for its miracle cost when you draw it if it’s the first card you drew this turn.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Sylvan Colossus</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1GG</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Elemental </type>
 <pt>3/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Reach
Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, you may draw a card. If this is the fifth time this ability has resolved this turn, you may cast up to one instant or sorcery spell from your hand without paying its mana cost. </text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Void Tome</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>At the beginning of your upkeep, remove all charge counters from Void Tome.
Whenever you cast an instant or sorcery spell, put a charge counter on Void Tome.
T, Sacrifice Void Tome: Search your library for an instant or sorcery card with mana value equal to the number of charge counters on Void Tome, exile it, then shuffle. Until end of turn, you may cast that card without paying its mana cost.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ravenify</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Counter target spell. Its controller creates a 1/1 blue Bird creature token with flying.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Tal Dagoth, Lord of Nightmares</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Hydra Nightmare </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Trample, haste
Whenever a card is put into your graveyard from anywhere, Tal Dagoth, Lord of Nightmares and each other Nightmare creature you control gets +1/+1 until end of turn.
If you would draw or mill a card while your library has no cards in it, if Tal Tagoth is in your graveyard, instead it deals 1 damage to each opponent.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Trunk Hurler Kami</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Giant Spirit </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice a land: You may put a land card from your hand onto the battlefield.
Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, Trunk Hurler Kami deals 1 damage to any target.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vircek Broodwarden</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>2G</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Vircek </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever another permanent card is put into your graveyard from anywhere other than the battlefield, create a 1/1 red Vircek creature token with haste. If this is the third time this ability has triggered this turn, return Vircek Broodwarden from your graveyard to your hand.
Viral 3 (Whenever this card is put into your graveyard from anywhere, mill three cards.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vircek Hellion</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>3G</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Vircek Hellion </type>
 <pt>5/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Trample
Whenever Vircek Hellion or another creature card is put into your graveyard from anywhere, if Vircek Hellion is on the battlefield or in your graveyard, creatures you control get +1/+1 until end of turn.
Viral 5 (Whenever this card is put into your graveyard from anywhere, mill five cards.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Detritus Sovereign</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Spirit </type>
 <pt>*/*</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Detritus Sovereign’s power and toughness are each equal to the number of creature cards and land cards in your graveyard.
Scavenge—Discard two cards (Discard two cards, Exile this card from your graveyard: Put a number of +1/+1 counters equal to this card’s power on target creature. Scavenge only as a sorcery.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Goblet of Victory</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add CU.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Dam Key</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add R.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Transcendent Epiphany</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>RRR</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice all permanents you control and discard you hand. Search your graveyard and/or library for up to three instant or sorcery cards, reveal them, put them into your hand and shuffle. Add three mana in any combination of colors.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Inner Sun</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Add one mana of any color.
Storm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each spell cast before it this turn.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Elesh Norn's Subjugation</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>H/WH/W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Put target creature card from your graveyard onto the battlefield under your control. That creature becomes a Phyrexian artifact in addition to its other types.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Sheoldred's Derision</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>H/BH/B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Target player reveals their hand. You choose a card from it. That player exiles that card and gets a poison counter.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Urabrask's Redemption</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>H/RH/R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>You may put an artifact or creature card from your hand onto the battlefield. If that card is a creature, it gains haste and becomes a Phyrexian artifact in addition to its other types. Sacrifice it at the beginning of the next end step.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vorinclex's Conscription</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>H/GH/G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Search your library for a creature card with mana value 2 or less, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle. That creature becomes a Phyrexian artifact in addition to its other types.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Virulent Hulk</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>2GG</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Vircek </type>
 <pt>6/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Trample, wither (This deals damage to creatures in the form of -1/-1 counters.)
At the beginning of each end step, if five or more cards have been put into your graveyard from anywhere this turn, you may return Virulent Hulk from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Insatiable Hivequeen</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Vircek </type>
 <pt>3/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Trample
Whenever a creature you control deals combat damage to a player, you may sacrifice it. If you do, discard a card, then draw cards equal to its power.
Dredge 3 (If you would draw a card, you mill three cards instead. If you do, return this card from your graveyard to your hand. Otherwise, draw a card.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ignite the Ichor</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Add RWB.
Flashback—R, Sacrifice a land. (You may cast this card from your graveyard for its flashback cost. Then exile it.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vircek Shapeshifter</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>RG</color>
 <manacost>2RG</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Vircek Shapeshifter </type>
 <pt>4/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Haste, changeling (This card is every creature type.)
R/G, Discard a card, Sacrifice a permanent: Return Vircek Shapeshifter from your graveyard to the battlefield.
Viral 4 (Whenever this card is put into your graveyard from anywhere, mill four cards.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>From Earth To Sky</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Create a 2/1 green Insect creature token with flying for each creature card in your graveyard.
Flashback 2G (You may cast this card from your graveyard for its flashback cost. Then exile it.)
Dredge 4 (If you would draw a card, you mill four cards instead. If you do, return this card from your graveyard to your hand. Otherwise, draw a card.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vircek Swarm Invasion</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>UBRG</color>
 <manacost>2UBRG</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Vircek Swarm Invasion deals X damage to any target, where X is the total power of creature cards in your graveyard.
Viral 4 (Whenever this card is put into your graveyard from anywhere, mill four cards.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Sickening Shadow</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Sickening Shadow deals 3 damage to any target.
You may cast Sickening Shadow from your graveyard as long as you’re part of the hive. (You’re part of the hive when your library has at most half as many cards as it did at the start of the game.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Artery Drinker</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>2B</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Horror </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice a creature: Put a -1/-1 counter on up to one target creature and create a Blood token. (It’s an artifact with “1, T, Discard a card, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a card.”)
Sacrifice an artifact: Target opponent loses 1 life and you gain 1 life.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Eldrazi Spirit Leech</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>3B</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Eldrazi Nightmare </type>
 <pt>0/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>If a permanent being put into a graveyard causes a triggered ability of a permanent you control to trigger, that ability triggers an additional time.
Whenever Eldrazi Spirit Leech or another nontoken creature dies, create a colorless 0/1 Eldrazi Spawn creature token. It has “Sacrifice this creature: Add C.”</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Psychic Ascension</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1UU</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Choose a sequence of card names, then exile that many cards from the bottom of your library in order from bottom to top. If the names of the exiled cards match the chosen sequence of names in order exactly, Psychic Ascension deals X damage divided as you choose among any number of targets, where X is the total mana value of the exiled cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Unleash the Hexgorger</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>UG</color>
 <manacost>GU</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Split second (As long as this spell is on the stack, players can’t cast spells or activate abilities that aren’t mana abilities.)
Counter target spell, activated, or trigger ability.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Psychic Inversion</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>3UU</manacost>
 <cmc>5</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Target opponent exiles cards from the top of their library until they exile a nonland card. You may cast that card without paying its mana cost.
Mindstorm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each card you’ve looked at from the top of a library this turn. You may choose new targets for the copies.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vircek Extraction</name>
 <set rarity="common">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>B</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Target player reveals their hand. You choose a card from it with mana value 3 or less. That player discards that card.
Viral 3 (Whenever this card is put into your graveyard from anywhere, mill three cards.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Dissonant Inquisitor</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>3</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact - Construct Horror </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Dissonant Inquisitor enters, target player discards two cards at random.
Evoke BB (You may cast this spell for its evoke cost. If you do, it’s sacrificed when it enters the battlefield.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Great Hunt</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill The Great Hunt at the beginning of combat on your turn if you control seven or more creatures. When you do, draw a card for each creature you control. Untap those creatures. They each gain haste until end of turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Yageki Truth Seeker</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Bird Rogue Wizard </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Instant and sorcery spells you cast cost 1 less to cast.
Magecraft — Whenever you cast or copy an instant or sorcery spell, venture into the dungeon. (Enter the first room or advance to the next room.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ancestral Favor</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Tap an untapped creature you control: Untap up to one target land.
Whenever you fulfill a prophecy, create X 1/1 black and white Spirit creature tokens with flying, where X is the number of creatures you control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Dawn of Growth</name>
 <set rarity="common">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Until end of turn, whenever you tap a land for mana, or whenever a land you control enters, add one mana of any color.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Borderland Druid</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>2G</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Snow Creature - Elf Warrior Cleric </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Trample
Whenever you cast a creature spell, take the initiative.
Tap an untapped creature you control: Add one mana of any color.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Phyrexian Rampage</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>3G</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Untap up to one target creature. It gets +1/+1 and gains haste and infect until end of turn. (That creature deals damage to creatures in the form of -1/-1 counters and to players in the form of poison counters.)
Storm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each spell cast before it this turn. You may choose new targets for the copies.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Revenge of the Dreadents</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Destroy target noncreature, nonbasic permanent.
Overload 1WBG (You may cast this spell for its overload cost. If you do, change its text by replacing all instances of “target” with “each”.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Soul Projection</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>UG</color>
 <manacost>GU</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever a creature you control enters, if you cast it from your hand, you may search your hand and/or library for a noncreature, nonland card with equal mana value and exile it, then shuffle. If you do, you may cast that card without paying its mana cost.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Grafted Spy Network</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>H/U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Splice onto instant or sorcery H/U (As you cast an instant or sorcery spell, you may reveal this card from your hand and pay its splice cost. If you do, add this card’s effects to that spell.)
Surveil 3 (Look at the top three cards of your library, then put any number of them into your graveyard and the rest on top of your library in any order.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Demanifest</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>UU</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Counter target spell.
Surge—Pay 3 life. (You may cast this spell for its surge cost if you or a teammate has cast another spell this turn.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Coming of the Mother Storm</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill The Coming of the Mother Storm as an instant if you’ve cast the same instant or sorcery spell twice this turn. When you do, until end of turn, whenever you cast an instant or sorcery spell, you may copy it and you may choose new targets for the copy.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Chart the Mind</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Fateseal 3 (To fateseal 3, look at the top three cards of an opponent’s library, then put any number of them on the bottom of that player’s library and the rest on top in any order.)
Plunder target opponent for 1. (Look at the top card of target opponent’s library. You may exile it face down. If you do, you may play that card using mana of any color for as long as it remains exiled.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Os'Uman, Keeper of the Keys</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>WU</color>
 <manacost>WU</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Creature - Construct </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever Os’Uman, Keeper of the Keys or another historic permanent you control enters, if you have not completed a dungeon this turn, venture into the dungeon. Otherwise, draw a card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mouse Dragon</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Mouse Dragon </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
Whenever you discard Mouse Dragon or another card, Mouse Dragon deals 1 damage to any target.
Cycling R (R, Discard this card: Draw a card.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Periphery Stalker</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>UB</color>
 <manacost>UB</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Nightmare Horror </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Haunt (When this creature dies, exile it haunting target creature.)
You control the creature Periphery Stalker haunts.
When the creature Periphery Stalker haunts dies, shuffle Periphery Stalker into your library.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vircek Plaguebearer</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>1B</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Vircek </type>
 <pt>4/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Haste, deathtouch, decayed (It can’t block. When it attacks, sacrifice it at end of combat.)
At the beginning of your upkeep, you may pay 2 life. If you do, return Vircek Plaguebearer from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Dig of the Century</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>WR</color>
 <manacost>XXRW</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Until end of turn, whenever a card leaves your graveyard, create a Treasure token.
Return up to X target permanent cards from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Galactic Palm</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>UR</color>
 <manacost>XUR</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Reveal the top card of your library. Galactic Palm deals damage equal to that card’s mana value to any target. Put that card into your hand. Repeat this process X times.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Kyurem White</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>UR</color>
 <manacost>4UR</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Dragon Ice Pokemon </type>
 <pt>5/5</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
When Kyurem White enters or leaves the battlefield, you may search your library for an instant or sorcery card, exile it, then shuffle. Until end of turn, you may cast it without paying its mana cost.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Drowned Queen</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>UB</color>
 <manacost>UB</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact - Vehicle </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Islandwalk
Whenever The Drowned Queen attacks, surveil X, where X is the total power of creatures crewing it.
Divination — At the beginning of each end step, plunder target opponent for X, where X is the number of cards you’ve looked at from the top of a library this turn.
Crew 3</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Burning Sunset Kirin</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WR</color>
 <manacost>5RW</manacost>
 <cmc>7</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Dragon Spirit </type>
 <pt>7/5</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying, haste, first strike, lifelink
Whenever a permanent you control becomes the target of a spell or ability, you may shuffle that permanent into your library, then reveal cards from the top of your library until you reveal a permanent card. Put that card onto the battlefield and the rest on the bottom of your library in a random order.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Chosen One</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WU</color>
 <manacost>8WU</manacost>
 <cmc>10</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Warrior </type>
 <pt>5/5</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Exalted (Whenever a creature you control attacks alone, that creature gets +1/+1 until end of turn.)
When The Chosen One enters, fulfill a prophecy you own.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Glare of the Morotum Eye</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>1R</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Exile target spell. You may cast a copy of it for as long as it remains exiled. At the beginning of its owner’s next upkeep, return that card from exile to its owner’s hand.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Rath Nokar, City of Fire</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add C.
T, Pay 2 life: Add BR.
BR, T, Sacrifice Rath Nokar, City of Fire: It deals 4 damage to any target and you gain 4 life.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Nerevara, Radiant Justicar</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>6WW</manacost>
 <cmc>8</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Creature - Archon </type>
 <pt>8/8</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
When Nerevara, Radiant Justicar enters, destroy all lands, then each player creates a Treasure token for each land card in their graveyard.
When Nerevara leaves the battlefield, destroy all creatures, then each player may return any number of land cards from their graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Rusted Sojourner</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Construct </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Rusted Sojourner enters, exile target nonland permanent. When Rusted Sojourner leaves the battlefield, return the exiled card to its owner’s hand.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Cosmic Conscription</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>BR</color>
 <manacost>1BR</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Target opponent reveals their hand. You choose a permanent card from it. Put that card onto the battlefield under your control. If it’s a creature, it gains haste. Sacrifice it at the beginning of the next end step.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Shape the Shadows</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>UG</color>
 <manacost>GGUU</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Create a token that’s a copy of target permanent.
Storm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each spell cast before it this turn. You may choose new targets for the copies.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Rambunctious Scallywag</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>2U</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Pirate </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Rambunctious Scallywag enters, gain control of target artifact for as long as you control Rambunctious Scallywag.
Skirmish — As long as an opponent controls a spell, Rambunctious Scallywag has flash.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Maescia, the Flame of Autumn</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>2R</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Faerie Wizard </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
Flying
When Maescia, the Flame of Autumn enters, return up to one target instant or sorcery card from your graveyard to your hand. Add three mana in any combination of colors.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Abzan Scorpion Witch</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Insect Wizard </type>
 <pt>0/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add W, B, or G.
Outlast 1 (1, T: Put a +1/+1 counter on this creature. Outlast only as a sorcery.)
Room abilities of the final rooms of dungeons you own trigger an additional X times, where X is Abzan Scorpion Witch’s power.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Onslaught of the Shadow Legion</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill Onslaught of the Shadow Legion at the beginning of the end step if eight or more creatures you control have died this turn. When you do, put all creature cards from all graveyards onto the battlefield under your control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Deranged Witness</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Elf Druid </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Deranged Witness enters, return target card from your graveyard to your hand.
Delirium — Whenever you cast a spell, if there are four or more card types among cards in your graveyard, create a 1/1 green Squirrel creature token.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Vampiric Ascendancy</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>RRR</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Pay 1 life: Create a Blood token. (It’s an artifact with “1, T, Discard a card, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a card.”)
Whenever you discard a card, you may pay 1 life. If you do, exile that card from your graveyard. You may play it from exile this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Blessing of Makahala</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill The Blessing of Makahala as an instant when you control a creature with power ten or greater. When you do, double that creature’s power and it gains lifelink, flying, deathtouch, haste, and trample until end of turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Consult the Archives</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>U</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Scry 2, then draw a card.
If you’ve fulfilled a prophecy this turn, you may return Consult the Archives to your hand as it resolves.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Waterfall Palace</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Mountain Forest Plains Island </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>(T: Add R, G, W, or U.)
RGWU, T, Sacrifice Waterfall Palace: Copy target instant or sorcery spell for each creature you control. You may choose new targets for the copies.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Oligarch's Cathedral</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Island Swamp Mountain Forest </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>(T: Add U, B, R, or G.)
UBRG, T, Sacrifice Oligarch’s Cathedral: Discard your hand, then draw seven cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>City of Bells</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Forest Plains Island Swamp </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>(T: Add G, W, U, or B.)
GWUB, T, Sacrifice City of Bells: Put X +1/+1 counters on target creature, where X is the number of spells you’ve cast this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ruined Metropolis</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Swamp Mountain Forest Plains </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>(T: Add B, R, G, or W.)
BRGW, T, Sacrifice Ruined Metropolis: Create a 1/1 colorless Sand creature token for each land you control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Industrial Pantheon</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land - Plains Island Swamp Mountain </type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>(T: Add W, U, B, or R.)
WUBR, T, Sacrifice Industrial Pantheon: Return target artifact or creature card from your graveyard to the battlefield. It gains haste and must attack this turn if able.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Golgari Plaguecrafter</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Wizard </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Golgari Plaguecrafter enters, draw a card.
Dredge 4 (If you would draw a card, you mill four cards instead. If you do, return this card from your graveyard to your hand. Otherwise, draw a card.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Chaos Consumer</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Horror </type>
 <pt>*/*</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Trample, haste
Chaos Consumer’s power and toughness are each equal to the number of cards you own in exile.
Escape—1, Exile three cards from your graveyard. (You may cast this card from your graveyard for its escape cost.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Dark Cosmic Jhin</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>4</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Creature - Demon </type>
 <pt>4/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Pay 1 life: Return target land card from your graveyard to the battlefield.
Whenever Dark Cosmic Jhin is put on the bottom of your library from anywhere, you may reveal it. If you do, it deals 4 damage to any target.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Northern Sunrise</name>
 <set rarity="common">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Snow Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Mill cards until you mill a land card. You may put a land card from your graveyard onto the battlefield.
Take the initiative.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Faile, Caretaker of Heirlooms</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>G</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Faerie </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
When Faile, Caretaker of Heirlooms enters, create a Treasure token.
Exile two other creature cards from your graveyard: Create a Treasure token. Activate this ability only if Faile is in your graveyard.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Student of Butchery</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>W</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Zombie Knight </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Level up—Sacrifice a creature. (Sacrifice a creature: Put a level counter on this. Level up only as a sorcery.)
LEVEL 2-6
3/3

LEVEL 7+
4/4
</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Icehammer Keep</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Snow Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add W or U.
Avalanche — Spells your opponents cast cost 1 more to cast for each land that’s entered the battlefield under your control this turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Zabor, Arcane Puppeteer</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WUB</color>
 <manacost>WUB</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Wizard </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>1, Sacrifice a creature: Put up to one creature card from your hand onto the battlefield. Activate only as a sorcery.
1, Return a creature you control to its owner’s hand: Put target creature card from your graveyard onto the battlefield. Activate only as a sorcery.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Furious Tutor</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>BR</color>
 <manacost>BR</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Search your library for a card, exile it face down, then shuffle. You may look at and play that card until the end of your next turn.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Pyre of the Coven</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>3</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever a permanent is put into your graveyard from the battlefield, Pyre of the Coven deals 1 damage to any target.
Sacrifice Pyre of the Coven: Return target Shaman, Warlock, or Wizard creature card from your graveyard to the battlefield. Activate only as a sorcery.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Cackling Amethyst</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Cackling Amethyst enters, target opponent enters a nightmare. (The nightmare ends when that player enters a dream or another nightmare.)
Whenever an opponent enters a nightmare, you may pay 2 life. If you do, return target noncreature card from your graveyard to your hand.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ascendant Ascetic</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Monk Construct </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, creatures you control get +1/+1 until end of turn. Untap those creatures.
Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, you may draw a card. If you do, discard a card.
URW: Ascendant Ascetic becomes an enchantment. (It’s no longer an artifact creature.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Whisk to Safety</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>You and permanents you control gain hexproof and indestructible until end of turn. If you are in a dungeon, retreat from the dungeon until you are no longer in a dungeon, then take the initiative.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Phyrexian Trading Post</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>H</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>H, T, Discard a card: You gain 4 life.
H, T, Pay 1 life: Create a 0/1 white Phyrexian Goat artifact creature token.
H, T, Sacrifice a creature: Return target artifact card from your graveyard to your hand.
H, T, Sacrifice an artifact: Draw a card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Beloved Scout</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Dog Scout Construct </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever Beloved Scout enters, surveil 2.
Beloved Scout can’t block.
Whenever you expand the frontier, you may create a token that’s a copy of Beloved Scout. (You expand the frontier when a land you control enters that does not share a name with another land you control.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Dubious Recompense</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>UU</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Gain control of target spell you don’t control. That spell’s controller creates X 1/1 blue Beeble creature tokens, where X is that spell’s mana value.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Fiddlestick Slasher</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>3</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Scarecrow </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Fiddlestick Slasher dies, draw two cards.
Wicked (You may cast this creature from your graveyard without paying its mana cost by sacrificing a number of permanents equal to its mana value.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Chromatic Snare</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Choose one —
• Manifest target spell unless its controller pays 3. (To manifest a card, put it onto the battlefield face down as a 2/2 creature. Turn it face up any time for its mana cost if it’s a creature card.)
• Manifest the top card of your library.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Calculated Clairvoyance</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>XYU</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Discover X a total of Y times. (Exile cards from the top of your library until you exile a nonland card with mana value X or less. Cast it without paying its mana cost or put it into your hand. Put the rest on the bottom in a random order.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Probe the Depths</name>
 <set rarity="rare" splitterPath="/Probe the Depths.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <related attach="attach">Augur of the Abyss</related>
 <manacost>XU</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Return up to X target instant or sorcery cards from your graveyard to your hand.
Disturb 2U (You may cast this card from your graveyard transformed for its disturb cost.)
---
(Back): Augur of the Abyss</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Augur of the Abyss</name>
 <set rarity="rare" splitterPath="/Augur of the Abyss.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Jellyfish Wizard </type>
 <pt>1/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Magecraft — Whenever you cast or copy an instant or sorcery spell, fateseal 1 and create a Treasure token. (To fateseal 1, look at the top card of an opponent’s library, then you may put it on the bottom of that player’s library.)
If Augur of the Abyss would be put into a graveyard from anywhere, shuffle it into its owner’s library instead.
---
(Front): Probe the Depths</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Book of Silenced Screams</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>2U</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Book of Silenced Screams enters, choose one —
• Gain control of target permanent for as long as you control Book of Silenced Screams.
• You may cast target instant or sorcery card from an opponent’s graveyard without paying its mana cost.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Terracotta Champion</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Construct Warrior </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Terracotta Champion enters or dies, choose one that hasn’t been chosen yet — 
• Destroy target permanent with mana value 3 or less.
• Return another target permanent card with mana value 3 or less from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Forgotten Crypt</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>7</manacost>
 <cmc>7</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Pay 1 life: Target nonland permanent phases out. (Treat it and anything attached to it as though they don’t exist until its controller’s next turn.)
T: Return target permanent from your graveyard to the battlefield under your control. It gains phasing. (This phases in or out before you untap during each of your untap steps. While it’s phased out, it’s treated as though it doesn’t exist.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Weeping Giant</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>3</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Tap an untapped artifact you control: If you control no creatures, you may search your library for a land card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle. If you do not, add one mana of any color instead.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Nokuum, Dynasty Oracle</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Zombie Wizard </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Nokuum, Dynasty Oracle enters, you get a monarchy counter.
Whenever you get a monarchy counter, each creature you control explores.
Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, you may create a 2/2 black Zombie create token.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Cvareh, Visionary Artificer</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WU</color>
 <manacost>WU</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Planeswalker - Cvareh </type>
 <loyalty>3</loyalty>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>[+1]: Investigate. (Create a colorless Clue artifact token with “2, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a card.”)
[0]: Detain target nonland permanent. (Until your next turn, that permanent can’t attack or block and its activated abilities can’t be activated.)
[-2]: Create a Cvareh’s Relay artifact token with “Artifact spells you cast cost 1 less to cast” and “Activated abilities of artifacts you control cost 1 less to activate.”
</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Nihkianbi, Wasteland Mimic</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Bird Horror </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
Flying
When Nihkianbi, Wasteland Mimic enters, copy up to one target instant or sorcery spell an opponent controls unless that opponent pays 3. You may choose new targets for the copy.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Binding of Ykak Morar</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>W</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment - Saga </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>
Exile target creature until The Binding of Ykak Morar leaves the battlefield.
You gain life equal to the exiled creature’s power.
Create X 1/1 white Soldier creature tokens, where X is the exiled creature’s power.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Koaru, Poet of Thunder</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1WW</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Planeswalker - Koaru </type>
 <loyalty>4</loyalty>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>[+2]: Until the beginning of your next turn, you may cast historic spells as though they had flash.
[-1]: Search your library for a historic card, reveal it, then shuffle and put that card on top.
[-3]: You may put a historic permanent card from your hand onto the battlefield.
[-7]: You get an emblem with, “Historic spells you cast have storm.”
</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Stormlight Archive</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Enchantment - Saga </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>(As this Saga enters and after your draw step, add a lore counter. Sacrifice after IV.)
The Way of Kings — Put an indestructible counter on target historic permanent you control.
Words of Radiance — Search your library for a historic card, reveal it, put it into your hand, then shuffle.
Oathbringer — Destroy all creatures. You gain 1 life for each creature destroyed this way.
Rhythm of War — Return up to one target historic permanent card from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Daratea, Guardian of Ysanai</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Elf Cleric </type>
 <loyalty>2</loyalty>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever an opponent casts a spell, choose one — 
+1: • Amass Elves 1.
-3: • Create a Food token.
-8: • Take the initiative.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Bellerophon</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Pegasus </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
Flying, horsemanship
Sacrifice Bellerophon: Counter target spell unless its controller pays 2.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Varu, the Crimson Fox</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Planeswalker - Varu </type>
 <loyalty>3</loyalty>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>[+1]: Take the initiative.
[-3]: Search your library for a creature card with an Adventure, reveal it, put it into your hand, then shuffle.
[-4]: You get an emblem with “Whenever you complete a dungeon, create a 5/5 red Dragon creature token with flying and haste.”
</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Heir of the God-Pharaoh</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>3WW</manacost>
 <cmc>5</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Noble </type>
 <pt>3/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever a token enters under your control, draw a card.
Tokens you control are Blood, Clue, Food, and Treasure in addition to their other types and have all associated abilities of those types.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Destria, Nova Summoner</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>2R</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Planeswalker - Destria </type>
 <loyalty>1</loyalty>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>[+1]: Draw two cards, then discard two cards.
[0]: Create a token that’s a copy of target creature card in your graveyard. It gains haste. Sacrifice it at the beginning of the next end step.
[-1]: You may put a creature card from your hand onto the battlefield. That creature gains haste. Sacrifice the creature at the beginning of the next end step.
</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Broken Altar</name>
 <set rarity="mythic" splitterPath="/The Broken Altar.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <related attach="attach">Interitus, Darkness Unleashed</related>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Sacrifice a creature: Put a loyalty counter on The Broken Altar.
B: Transform The Broken Altar. Activate only as a sorcery.
---
(Back): Interitus, Darkness Unleashed</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Interitus, Darkness Unleashed</name>
 <set rarity="mythic" splitterPath="/Interitus, Darkness Unleashed.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Planeswalker - Interitus </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever a creature dies, put a loyalty counter on Interitus, Darkness Unleashed.
[-X]: Distribute X -1/-1 counters onto any number of target creatures.
[-X]: Draw X cards and lose X life.
[-X]: Each opponent loses X life and you gain X life.
---
(Front): The Broken Altar</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Quatz, Hammer of the Citadel</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>6</manacost>
 <cmc>6</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Creature - Construct </type>
 <pt>4/5</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
Flying, lifelink
When Quatz, Hammer of the Citadel enters, it fights up to one target creature.
Evoke R/GW (You may cast this spell for its evoke cost. If you do, it’s sacrificed when it enters the battlefield.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Colossal Guardian</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Construct </type>
 <pt>*/*</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Colossal Guardian’s power and toughness are each equal to the number of artifacts you control.
Sacrifice an artifact: Colossal Guardian gains protection from all colors until end of turn. (This creature can’t be blocked, targeted, dealt damage, enchanted, or equipped by anything that’s white, blue, black, red, or green until end of turn.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Uriel, of the Eternal Flame</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Angel </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever a historic permanent you control enters, put a +1/+1 counter on up to one target creature.
At the beginning of your upkeep, return up to one target historic permanent card from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Eawen, Battle Librarian</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Elf Wizard </type>
 <pt>2/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
When Eawen, Battle Librarian enters, return target instant or sorcery card from your graveyard to the battlefield face-down as a 2/2 creature.
W: Return target creature you control to its owner’s hand.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Spark of Nadeon</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>WU</color>
 <manacost>WU</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment - Saga </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>(As this Saga enters and after your draw step, add a lore counter. Sacrifice after III.)
I — Exile target nonland permanent an opponent controls.
II — Create Nadeon, a legendary 0/0 white and blue Construct artifact creature token with “Modular X”, where X is the exiled card’s mana value.
III — Tap up to X target permanents, where X is the number of artifacts you control. Put a stun counter on those permanents.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Casira of the Ancient Path</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>WG</color>
 <manacost>1GW</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Elf Druid </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever Casira of the Ancient Path attacks, create a Mirari’s Wake token. (It’s a 3GW green and white enchantment token with “Creatures you control get +1/+1” and “Whenever you tap a land for mana, add one mana of any type that land produced.”)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Foundry Hedron</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add C.
T: Discard an artifact card: Add X, where X is the mana value of the discarded card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Magus Automata</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact - Construct Wizard </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Draw a card, then discard a card.
T: Turbocharge target artifact you control. (Each other artifact you control has all activated and triggered abilities of that artifact until end of turn. Sacrifice that artifact at the beginning of the next end step.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ashvicar's Tome of Illusion</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add two mana in any combination of colors.
Whenever you cast your third instant or sorcery spell this turn, you may create a token that’s a copy of Ashvicar’s Tome of Illusion.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Undying Conflict</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>BR</color>
 <manacost>BR</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Return two target creature cards from graveyards to the battlefield under your control. Those creatures fight. (Each deals damage equal to its power to the other.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Settlers of Catan</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>WUG</color>
 <manacost>G/WU</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Join forces — Starting with you, each player may pay any amount of mana. Each player creates X 1/1 green and white Settler creature tokens, where X is the total amount of mana paid this way, then each player draws a card for each creature they control.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Journey Through Oblivion</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Return target creature you control to its owner’s hand. If you do, you may discard a creature card. If you do, you may return a creature card from your graveyard to the battlefield.
Flashback W (You may cast this card from your graveyard for its flashback cost. Then exile it.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ruinous Siphon</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>BB</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Casualty 1 (As you cast this spell, you may sacrifice a creature with power 1 or greater. When you do, copy this spell.)
Target player reveals their hand. You choose a card from it. That player discards that card. Add B equal to its mana value.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Architect of Discord</name>
 <set rarity="rare" splitterPath="/Architect of Discord.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <related attach="attach">Awareness Distortion</related>
 <manacost>4</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Eldrazi </type>
 <pt>4/4</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Ward 4 (Whenever this creature becomes the target of a spell or ability an opponent controls, counter it unless that player pays 4.)
Whenever Architect of Discord attacks, you control defending player until end of combat.
---
(Back): Awareness Distortion</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Awareness Distortion</name>
 <set rarity="rare" splitterPath="/Awareness Distortion.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Instant</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>End the turn unless the player whose turn it is pays 2. (Exile all spells and abilities from the stack. The player whose turn it is discards down to their maximum hand size. Damage wears off, and “this turn” and “until end of turn” effects end.)
---
(Front): Architect of Discord</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Time-Fortress Temple</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add B.
T, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Time-Fortress Temple: Search your library for a Plains or a Forest card and put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Shadow Garden Temple</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add G.
T, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Shadow Garden Temple: Search your library for a Swamp or Island card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Frostblossom Temple</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add R.
T, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Frostblossom Temple: Search your library for a Island or Plains card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Firestorm Temple</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add W.
T, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Firestorm Temple: Search your library for a Mountain or Swamp card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Blood Shaman Temple</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add U.
T, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Blood Shaman Temple: Search your library for a Forest or Mountain card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Alchemist's Familiar</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Horror </type>
 <pt>1/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Alchemist’s Familiar enters, create a Blood, Clue, Food, or Treasure token.
3, T, Sacrifice a Blood, Clue, Food, and Treasure: Target player sacrifices three creatures and discards three cards.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Sudden Rage</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>R</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment - Aura </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
Split second (As long as this spell is on the stack, players can’t cast spells or activate abilities that aren’t mana abilities.)
Enchant creature
Whenever another creature enters the battlefield, enchanted creature fights it.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ruins of Gitrog Bog</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>At the beginning of your upkeep, sacrifice a land or sacrifice Ruins of Gitrog Bog.
You may play an additional land on each of your turns.
Whenever a land card is put into your graveyard from anywhere, draw a card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Sightless Surveyor</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>4</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Artifact - Construct Horror </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Skulk (That creature can’t be blocked by creatures with greater power.)
When Sightless Surveyor leaves the battlefield, create two 4/4 colorless Construct Horror artifact creature tokens.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Psychopomp's Ferry</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact - Vehicle </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Voidwalk (This creature can only block while tapped and can only be blocked by tapped creatures.)
Sacrifice a creature: Psychopomp’s Ferry becomes an artifact creature in addition to its other types until end of turn.
Whenever Psychopomp’s Ferry deals combat damage to a player, return up to one target card from your graveyard to your hand.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Ghost Shadow Lotus</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>0</manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Put a -1/-1 counter on a creature you control: Tap or untap target permanent.
3: Proliferate. Only your opponents may activate this ability.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Enlightened Toad Shrine</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Discard a card: Create a Treasure token. (It’s an artifact with “T, Sacrifice this artifact: Add one mana of any color.”)
5WUBRG, T, Sacrifice Enlightened Toad Shrine: Create a 1/1 green Frog creature token for each card in your graveyard.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Zruareki Shrine</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add R, G, or W.
When Zruareki Shrine is put into a graveyard from the battlefield, if you control a creature named Zruareki, put two +1/+1 counters on it. Otherwise, create Zruareki, a legendary 2/2 red, green, and white Bird creature token with flying, haste, and vigilance.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Bone Valley Temple</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add R.
T, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Bone Valley Temple: Search your library for a Swamp or Forest card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mystic Wind Temple</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Land</type>
 <tablerow>0</tablerow>
 <text>T: Add U.
T, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Mystic Wind Temple: Search your library for a Plains or Swamp card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Despair Ex Machina</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>2UU</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Sorcery</type>
 <tablerow>3</tablerow>
 <text>Look at target opponent’s hand. You may cast a spell from among those cards without paying its mana cost.
Miracle UU (You may cast this card for its miracle cost when you draw it if it’s the first card you drew this turn.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Timespren</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Spirit </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Put target card from your graveyard on the bottom of your library: Scry 2.
Divination — While looking at cards from the top of your library, you may cast spells from among the cards you look at as though they had flash.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Lightning Conduit</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>2</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact - Elemental Golem </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Deathtouch, haste
Whenever another artifact you control enters, Lightning Conduit gets +1/+1 until end of turn.
1, Sacrifice Lightning Conduit: Copy target activated or triggered ability you control X times, where X is Lightning Conduit’s power.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Court of the Yellow King</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>U</color>
 <manacost>1U</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Court of the Yellow King enters or leaves the battlefield, create a token that’s a copy of up to one target creature, except it has illusory. (Whenever that creature becomes targeted, sacrifice it). </text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Rem, Wandering Terraturge</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>3</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact Planeswalker - Rem </type>
 <loyalty>2</loyalty>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever another artifact you control enters, put a loyalty counter on Rem, Wandering Terraturge.
[-X]: Untap up to X target artifacts.
[-XX]: Return up to X target artifact cards with mana value X or less from your graveyard to the battlefield.
</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Archdruid Vereyana</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Elf Druid </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flash
When Archdruid Vereyana enters, Choose one —
• Put any number of land cards from your hand onto the battlefield.
• Return any number of land cards from your graveyard to the battlefield.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Canon Hunter</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2H/W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Phyrexian Dragon </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying, vigilance
H/W, Sacrifice a historic permanent: Reveal cards from the top of your library until you reveal a historic card. Put that card into your hand and the rest on the bottom of your library in a random order. If you do, put two +1/+1 counters on Canon Hunter.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Stellar Calliope</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>XYW</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>0: Return up to one target historic permanent card from your graveyard to the battlefield with mana value X or less. Activate this ability no more than Y times each turn as a sorcery. (Artifacts, legendaries, and Sagas are historic.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Fallen God</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Historic permanents you control are Plains lands in addition to their other types. (They each have “T: Add W.”)
Historic permanents you control have exalted.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Oathcursed Blade</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact - Equipment </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Oathcursed Blade enters, create a 2/2 black Zombie Warrior creature token with menace.
Whenever equipped creature deals combat damage, venture into the dungeon that many times.
Equip 0</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Dorangrin of the Soulforge</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Dwarf Artificer </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever another creature you control dies, you may return it to the battlefield under your control, except its an artifact Equipment with “Equipped creature gets +X/+X, where X is this permanent’s mana value” and “Equip 0.”</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Conspicuous Saboteur</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Gnome Rogue </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying
T: Destroy target permanent you control. Investigate X times, where X is that permanent’s mana value. (Create a colorless Clue artifact token with “2, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a card.”)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Balan Voz, Upstart Conquerer</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Noble </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Balan Voz, Upstart Conquerer enters, search your library for a Plains card, reveal it, then shuffle. If an opponent controls more lands than you, you may put that land onto the battlefield. Otherwise put it into your hand.
Whenever a Plains you control enters, you become get a monarchy counter.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Mantle of Rule</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1WW</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>At the beginning of your upkeep, you get a monarchy counter.
At the beginning of each end step, create a Treasure token for each spell you’ve cast this turn.
Tap two untapped artifacts you control: Venture into the dungeon.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Curse of Generosity</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>2W</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Enchantment - Aura Curse </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Enchant opponent
Whenever enchanted player draws a card, you may draw a card.
Whenever a land enters under enchanted player’s control, you may create a Treasure token.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>The Dawn Lancet</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact - Equipment </type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>Equipped creature gets +2/+0.
Whenever equipped creature deals combat damage, create that many Blood tokens and that many Treasure tokens.
Equip 0</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Priest of the Crimson Oil</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Sphinx Artificer </type>
 <pt>1/3</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Whenever Priest of the Crimson Oil or another creature enters, create a Blood token.
T, Sacrifice a Blood artifact: Turbocharge target artifact you control. (Each other artifact you control has all activated and triggered abilities of that permanent until end of turn. Sacrifice it at the beginning of the next end step.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Execrable Urn</name>
 <set rarity="uncommon">JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost>1W</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>When Execrable Urn enters or leaves the battlefield, choose a card type other than land, then target player sacrifices a permanent of the chosen type.
2, Sacrifice Execrable Urn: Draw a card.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Gouda, Brave Companion</name>
 <set rarity="mythic" splitterPath="/Gouda, Brave Companion.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <related attach="attach">Gouda, Hardy Sort</related>
 <manacost>W</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Dog </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Soulbond (You may pair this creature with another unpaired creature when either enters the battlefield. They remain paired for as long as you control both of them.)
Whenever the creature Gouda, Brave Companion is paired with dies, transform Gouda, Brave Companion.
---
(Back): Gouda, Hardy Sort</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Gouda, Hardy Sort</name>
 <set rarity="mythic" splitterPath="/Gouda, Hardy Sort.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color>W</color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Dog </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Indestructible
Once per turn on your turn, you may copy an activated or triggered ability of a historic permanent you control.
---
(Front): Gouda, Brave Companion</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Spyder</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>1</manacost>
 <cmc>1</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Spider Construct </type>
 <pt>0/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Spyder can’t block.
T: Surveil 1.
When Spyder dies, create two tokens that are copies of it at the beginning of the next end step.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mirrors of Angashator</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost>4</manacost>
 <cmc>4</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may spend mana as though it were of any color to cast spells from your hand.
Cards you own outside the game are Lessons in addition to their other types.
Whenever you cast a spell, learn. (You may reveal a Lesson card you own from outside the game and put it into your hand, or discard a card to draw a card.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Finding of the Pirate King's Throne</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>At the beginning of your upkeep, you may fulfill Finding of the Pirate King’s Throne if you control three or more permanents owned .by an opponent. When you do, create twenty Treasure tokens. (They’re artifacts with “T, Sacrifice this artifact: Add one mana of any color.”)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Gluttonous Ghouls</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>B</color>
 <manacost>2B</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Spirit </type>
 <pt>1/1</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Haste, menace
Devour 1 (As this enters the battlefield, you may sacrifice any number of creatures. This creature enters the battlefield with that many +1/+1 counters on it.)
Gravestorm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each permanent put into a graveyard this turn.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Winter Is Coming</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill Winter Is Coming at the beginning of your upkeep if you control a snow land, another nonland permanent that is snow, and have a snow card in your graveyard. When you do, you get an emblem with “All permanents you control are snow” and “Tap two untapped snow permanents you control: Exile target nonland permanent. Return it to the battlefield under its owner’s control at the beginning of the next end step.”</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Mox Amethyst</name>
 <set rarity="mythic" splitterPath="/Mox Amethyst.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <related attach="attach">Korphirax, Sovereign Unsealed</related>
 <manacost>0</manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Artifact</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>T: Create a Treasure token. (It’s an artifact with “T, Sacrifice this artifact: Add one mana of any color.”)
GGGUUURRR, T: Transform Mox Amethyst.
---
(Back): Korphirax, Sovereign Unsealed</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Korphirax, Sovereign Unsealed</name>
 <set rarity="mythic" splitterPath="/Korphirax, Sovereign Unsealed.full.jpg" >JVC</set>
 <color>URG</color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Dragon </type>
 <pt>8/8</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Flying, trample, haste
Whenever you cast a spell, choose one —
• Target Dragon creature you control fights another target creature.
• Draw a card for each Dragon creature you control.
• Create a 5/5 red Dragon creature token with flying.
---
(Front): Mox Amethyst</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Starfist Battlemage</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>UG</color>
 <manacost>GU</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Creature - Human Warrior Wizard </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Starfist Battlemage enters, scry 2.
Divination — Whenever you look at cards from the top of a library, put that many +1/+1 counters on target creature.
Whenever a creature you control deals combat damage to a player, you may venture into the dungeon that many times.</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>A God from the Ashes</name>
 <set rarity="mythic">JVC</set>
 <color></color>
 <manacost></manacost>
 <cmc>0</cmc>
 <type>Prophecy</type>
 <tablerow>1</tablerow>
 <text>You may fulfill A God from the Ashes at the beginning of your upkeep if you control no permanents and have no cards in hand. When you do, shuffle your graveyard into your library, draw seven cards, then you get an emblem with “Discard a card: You may cast a spell from your hand without paying its mana cost.”</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Jebediah, First to Till</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>G</color>
 <manacost>1G</manacost>
 <cmc>2</cmc>
 <type>Legendary Creature - Human Scout </type>
 <pt>2/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>When Jebediah, First to Till enters, take the initiative.
Whenever you expand the frontier, create a Food token for each land you control and put a +1/+1 counter on each creature you control. (You expand the frontier when a land you control enters that does not share a name with another land you control.)</text>
</card>
<card>
 <name>Golden Mindscrambler</name>
 <set rarity="rare">JVC</set>
 <color>R</color>
 <manacost>2R</manacost>
 <cmc>3</cmc>
 <type>Artifact Creature - Construct Berserker </type>
 <pt>3/2</pt>
 <tablerow>2</tablerow>
 <text>Menace, haste
Whenever Golden Mindscrambler attacks, you may discard a card. If you do, Golden Mindscrambler deals damage equal to that card’s mana value to any target and you draw a card.</text>
</card>

<!-->Tokens</-->


</cards>
</cockatrice_carddatabase>